- All I was doing was just waking up, making breakfast,
- 내가하고 있었던 것은 단지 깨어 아침 식사를 만들고,
going down to Starbucks, buying my $6 latte or whatever,
스타 벅스에 가서 6 달러 커피를 사거나,
do my work at Starbucks,
내 직업은 스타 벅스로하고,
going home and going to bed.
집에 가서 잔다.
I was just thinking my lease is coming up
난 그냥 내 임대가오고 있다고 생각했다
and I’m going to have to pay $6,000(Singapore Dollar) to keep doing this
나는이 일을 계속하기로 6,000 드 - 르 (싱가포르 달러)를 지불해야한다
and I just thought, “Screw it.
난 그냥 "그것을 끼워 줄 알았는데.
"Let’s just leave.
"그냥 출발하자.
"I don’t need to be here.
"나는 여기에있을 필요는 없다.
"Let’s just leave.”
"그냥 출발하자"
- It’s absolute project impossible.
그것은 불가능한 절대적인 프로젝트입니다.
I couldn’t do it because I knew that it would make me
나는 그것이 나에게
so damn unhappy that I would do everything
내가 다 해줄 것을 불행하게하고있다
in my power to not go back.
내 힘으로 돌아 오지 않게한다.
I couldn’t imagine going back to that.
내가 다시 상상할 수 없습니다.
That would be crazy.
그것은 미쳐있을 것이다.
What are you talking about?
당신은 무엇에 대해 이야기하고 있습니까?
- Once something becomes your comfort zone,
- 당신의 안락 지대되면
it’s time to leave because
그것은 떠날 때가 있으니까
that keeps you constantly expanding.
그것은 당신을 지속적으로 확대시켜 계속합니다.
You expand yourself, definition of who you are.
당신은 자신을 확장하고 당신이 누구인지를 정의합니다.
You expand the places of where you become comfortable
편안하게 장소를 확대
in the world.
세계.
- Our commute to work.
- 우리의 출퇴근 통근.
We always wanted to travel for years, like super long term.
우리는 항상 오랜 같이 몇 년 동안 여행을하고 싶다고 생각했습니다.
- 100.
- 100.
- Okay, okay, I give you 120.
- 음, 그래, 난 당신이 120을 준다.
- We were living in the Silicon Valley.
- 우리는 실리콘 밸리에 살고있었습니다.
Most people are trying to get into the Silicon Valley
대부분의 사람들이 실리콘 밸리에 들어가는 것을 시도하고 있습니다
and we grew up there, so we were trying to get out.
우리는 거기에서 자랐기 때문에 우리는 탈출하려고했습니다.
It started out, I asked my boss.
그것이 시작된 내 상사에게 물었다.
We already, at Upwork, we have one day a week
우리는 이미 업 작업에서 일주일에 하루
that everybody in the entire company is remote.
회사 전체의 모두가 멉니 다.
You can work from home, and so I negotiated two days a week.
당신은 집에서 일을 할 수 있기 때문에 일주일에 2 일 협상했습니다.
And slowly, the two days a week became three, became four,
그리고 천천히 일주일에 2 일은 3가, 4가,
became five and then one point I think,
5 된 후,
I said as a joke to my boss at the time that
나는 그 때 내 상사에 농담으로 말했다
"Maybe I can work while I'm traveling."
"여행하는 동안 일할 수 있을지도 모른다."
Surprisingly, she was super supportive
놀랍게도, 그녀는 매우지지 적이었다
and one year later, here we are.
그리고 1 년 후, 여기에 있습니다.
- So the digital nomad thing is really different
- 디지털 유목민 것은 정말 다르다
from the traveler who's just here having fun.
여기 만 즐기는 여행에서.
They'll be here this weekend, maybe a week
이번 주말 이곳은 주 될지도 모른다
and then they're gone and on to the next place.
그 때 그들은하고 다음 위치로 이동합니다.
It's two very different lives.
그것은 두 개의 매우 다른 삶입니다.
- The biggest challenge though is dealing with time zones.
- 최대의 과제는 시간대를 치료하는 것입니다.
It's difficult to overlap from Asia with Europe
유럽과 아시아에서의 중복 어렵다
and the United States.
미국 사이에 체결되었다.
It means we end up working really crazy hours.
그것은 우리가 정말 미친 시간을 보내는 것을 의미합니다.
We usually start working around like 5 or 6 p.m.
우리는 일반적으로 5 또는 6시와 같이 일을 시작합니다.
and work until 2 a.m. or 3 a.m.
오전 2시 또는 오전 3 시까 지 일합니다.
When we were in Bali, it was way worse.
우리가 발리에있을 때, 그것은 더 나빴다.
I was working till 4am and .
나는 오전 4 시까 지 일하고 있었다.
- 5 a.m., 6 a.m. - Some, yeah.
- 오전 5시 오전 6시 - 일부, 그래.
- We started traveling two months after we got married
- 우리는 결혼하고 2 개월 후 출발했습니다
and one of our friends who we met traveling,
우리가 여행에 만난 친구 중 하나,
he called us the ultimate honeymooners.
그는 우리를 최고의 신혼 여행이라고 불렀다.
We're kind of on a never ending honeymoon.
우리는 결코 끝이없는 신혼 여행에 있습니다.
That definitely has its.
확실히 그것을 가지고 있습니다.
- That explains all the problems we have.
- 그것은 우리가 가지고있는 모든 문제를 설명합니다.
- I'm an engineer, and basically what I do
- 나는 엔지니어이며, 기본적으로 내가하고있는 것입니다
is I run two different SaaS services.
나는 두 개의 다른 SaaS 서비스를 운영하고 있습니까?
Singapore was where I had my last corporate job ever.
싱가포르는 내가 마지막으로 한 기업의 직장이 있던 자리였습니다.
I didn't want to keep building stuff for other people,
나는 다른 사람을 위해 물건을 계속 만드는 것을 원하지 않았습니다 만,
I wanted to build something for myself.
나는 자신을 위해 뭔가를 만들고 싶었습니다.
Then it got closer and closer to my lease coming to an end.
그럼, 임대가 끝나 가고 왔습니다.
And I was just looking at my life up until that point.
그리고 난 그 시점에 자신의 인생을보고 있었다 뿐이었다.
If I find a cheap place, how much is it going
내가 싼 장소를 찾으면 아무리하고 있습니까?
to cost for me to stay there for a month?
내가 한 달 동안 거기 체재 비용은?
I started looking on Agoda and I was like,
나는 Agoda 보이기 시작했습니다. 내가 그랬습니다.
"Oh my God, I can stay in a hotel for $1,000,
"오 나의 하나님, 나는 $ 1,000을 위해 호텔에 투숙 할 수 있습니다,
"which is 3 times less than my rent."
"이것은 집세의 3 배입니다."
Why has it taken me this long to realize
왜 이것이 실현하기까지 오랜 시간이 걸렸습니까?
that actually I could be doing all this work
실제로 나는이 모든 일을하고있을 가능성이있는
from Thailand or anywhere.
태국과 어디서나.
It's just kind of this epiphany moment
이러한 시대의 순간 같다
and I guess it all seems really obvious in retrospect.
내가 돌이켜 보면 정말 분명하다고 생각합니다.
Ever since that point, that was 2012 August,
그 시점 이후 2012 년 8 월이며,
I haven't stopped.
나는 멈추지 않았다.
- Being a digital nomad is about being able
- 디지털 유목민 인 것은
to live and work wherever you want.
당신이 어디에 있든 살아 일할 수 있습니다.
It's not about always having to be on the go,
그것은 항상 외출 중일 필요는 없습니다
moving from country to country, or city to city every week.
매주 국가에서 도시 또는 도시에서 도시로 이동합니다.
It's just about having the freedom to choose.
그냥 자유를 선택하는 것에 대하여입니다.
"I want to live in the country,
"나는 그 나라에서 살고 싶다
"and my company is in the city."
"우리 회사는 도시에있는"
You can do that.
할 수 있어요.
Or, "My company is in the city,
또는 "우리 회사가 거리에 있습니다.
"and I want to live."
"나는 살고 싶다"
"I don't want to come in and commute
"와서 통근 싶지 않아
"and waste gas money, and time."
"그리고 가스의 낭비와 시간."
So I think it's more about having that freedom
그래서 내가 그 자유를 가질 대해
and that choice more than anything else.
그 선택은 무엇보다 중요합니다.
- With Buffer I manage to work from any place.
- 버퍼를 사용하면 어디서든 작업 할 수 있습니다.
If I have internet, my laptop is my office.
나는 인터넷이 있으면, 내 노트북은 내 사무실입니다.
It doesn't quite matter where I am,
내가 어디에 있는지는 그다지 중요하지 않지만,
and that I really appreciate.
정말 감사합니다.
Could then be in the coffee shop in the morning,
아침에 다방에 들어갈 수있었습니다.
in the co-working space in the afternoon,
오후의 공동 작업 공간에서는
I only commute if I want to,
내가 원한다면 통근하는 것만으로,
and that's a super cool luxury for me.
그것은 나를 위해 매우 멋진 사치입니다.
I think since I joined Buffer I've been travelling
나는 Buffer에 합류 이후, 나는 여행하고 있다고 생각합니다
between 50 and 70% of my time, so I, based in Paris,
내 시간의 50 %에서 70 % 사이에서 파리에 본사를 둔 전
and I go outside of France
나는 프랑스의 외출
and I discover new places very, very often.
나는 새 위치를 매우 자주 발견합니다.
- One of the ways that have really started working
- 실제로 작업을 시작했다 방법의 하나
very differently the past,
과거와는 전혀 다른,
in particularly the past 20 years,
특히 지난 20 년간,
is that they have started working in other places
그들은 다른 곳에서 일을 시작하는 것입니다
than by their desks or workstations.
그들의 책상이나 워크 스테이션보다.
So this idea of flexible working, mobile working,
따라서 유연한 작업 모바일 작업,
itinerant working, the nomadic working,
순회 근무 유목민 취업,
all of these concepts,
이러한 모든 개념,
they cover more or less the same broad range
그들은 대체로 비슷 넓은 범위를 커버
of phenomenon that people,
사람들의
they don’t have to sit and work where the data is.
그들은 데이터가있는 장소에 앉거나 일할 필요가 없습니다.
- The whole digital nomad movement right now
- 지금의 디지털 유목민 운동 전체
is exploding like crazy.
미친 듯이 폭발하고있다.
When I look back three or four years ago
내가 3 년 4 년 전에 되돌아 보면
when I started out as a digital nomad,
내가 디지털 유목민으로 출발했을 때,
I remember we had our “The 4 Hour Work Week” meet up here
우리는 우리의 "The 4 Hour Work Week"여기서 만났어요
in Berlin and we met up in this bar and we were four people.
베를린에서는이 바에서 만나 우리는 4 명이었습니다.
And now over the years,
그리고 지금 몇 년 동안
we’re now having conferences for digital nomads
우리는 현재 디지털 유목민을위한 회의를 개최하고 있습니다
and there’s all these blogs, there’s all these events,
이러한 모든 블로그가 있지만 - 이러한 모든 이벤트가 있습니다.
there’s all these workshops,
이러한 모든 워크샵 있습니다.
there’s all these hubs and Facebook groups.
이러한 모든 허브와 Facebook 그룹이 있습니다.
It’s exploding and there’s all this new infrastructure
그것은 폭발적이 새로운 인프라는 모든 있습니다
that’s happening for digital nomads.
그것은 디지털 유목민에게 일어나고있는 것입니다.
- Location independence,
- 위치의 독립성,
digital nomads I suppose later have existed
내가 나중에 존재하고 있었다고 생각되는 디지털 유목민
for a long time and well before The 4-Hour Workweek.
긴 시간 동안 그리고 4 시간 노동 시간 전에 잘.
What I attempted to do in The 4-Hour Workweek was
내가 4 시간의 노동 시간에하려고 한 것은,
to try to codify and gather a framework
프레임 워크를 코드화하여 수집하려는
and a collection of tools for people who wanted
희망자를위한 도구 모음
to take advantage of time and location
시간과 장소를 이용하는
or mobility as currencies, now forty languages later.
현재 40 개 국어 이상의 통화로의 이동성을 제공합니다.
It seems like being a digital nomad,
그것은 디지털 유목민처럼 보이지만,
if you want to do that,
당신이 그것을 원한다면,
is available to more people than ever before.
어느 때보 다 많은 사람들이 사용할 수 있습니다.
As a function of technology and also just a mind shift.
기술의 기능뿐만 아니라 마음의 변화.
- I made a site called Nomad List
- Nomad List라는 사이트를 만든
which ranks the top 100 cities based on cost of living,
생활비를 기준으로 상위 100 개 도시를 선정,
temperature, weather, if there's nice places
기온, 날씨, 멋진 장소가있는 경우
to work, for example.
예를 들어, 일을한다.
That site when viral.
그 사이트는 바이러스 성입니다.
It went on the front page of Reddit,
그것은 Reddit의 첫 페이지에있었습니다.
it came on Hacker News, Product Hunt.
그것은 Hacker News, Product Hunt에있었습니다.
According to my data, my website the most popular place
내 데이터에 따르면, 내 웹 사이트는 가장 인기있는 장소
for nomads right now are Chiang Mai,
현재는 유목민을 위해 치앙마이,
still because traditionally the starting place
아직 전통적으로 출발
for digital nomads, Bangkok, Berlin, Budapest in Hungary,
디지털 유목민, 방콕, 베를린, 헝가리 부다페스트,
Ho Chi Minh City in Vietnam, Medellin in Colombia.
베트남 호치민시, 콜롬비아 메 델린.
They're all kind of low cost of living,
그들은 모든 종류의 생활비가 저렴하지만,
warm, with fast internet.
따뜻한 고속 인터넷.
- About 2 years ago, we opened Hubud which is the largest
- 약 2 년 전, 우리는 Hubud을 오픈했습니다.
and the first co-working space in Bali.
발리의 첫 번째 공동 작업 공간.
The funny thing happened after we opened
재미있는 것은 우리가 열린 후 일어난
which was it wasn’t people like us
그것은 우리 같은 사람이 아니었다
that started coming to the space.
그것은 우주에 온 시작했다.
It was this new kind of person
이 새로운 유형의 인물이었다
who called themselves digital nomads.
그는 자신을 디지털 유목민이라고 불렀다.
We had never heard the term digital nomad before we opened.
우리는 오픈하기 전에 디지털 유목 - 백성이라는 말을 들어 본 적이 없었습니다.
It was new to us.
그것은 우리에게는 새로운 것이었다.
But all of a sudden,
그러나 갑자기
we became kind of a mecca for digital nomads.
우리는 디지털 유목민의 메카가되었습니다.
We had developers, we have designers,
우리는 개발자를 안고있었습니다. 디자이너,
we have startup business development people.
우리는 시작 비즈니스 개발자가 있습니다.
We have photographers, we have videographers.
우리는 사진 작가가 비디오 작가가 있습니다.
It’s really the full gamut of what is out there.
실제로 거기에 있지만 전체 범위입니다.
We did a recent survey just last month and now about 90%
우리는 지난달 최근의 설문 조사를 실시했습니다. 현재는 약 90 %
of our members consider themselves digital nomads
우리 회원 중에는 디지털 유목민
or want to be digital nomads.
또는 디지털 유목민이되고 싶다
- This is a villa that's associated with Hubud,
- 이것은 Hubud에 연결된 별장입니다.
but they rent it out to different start ups
그러나 그들은 그것을 별도의 시작에 빌려준
or groups that come in.
또는 온 그룹.
We are renting it out for the month.
우리는 그 달에 빚진있다.
There's five rooms upstairs
위층에 5 개의 방이 있습니다
and we basically use the downstairs as our workspace
기본적으로 아래층을 우리의 작업 공간으로 사용하고 있습니다
and a place to have meals and things like that.
음식을 먹는 장소 등이 있습니다.
So Hacker Paradise started in the summer of 2014.
해커 파라다이스는 2014 년 여름에 시작되었습니다.
We had about 20 to 30 developers down
우리는 약 20 ~ 30 명의 개발자가있었습니다
in Costa Rica in the fall.
가을에는 코스타리카에서 개최됩니다.
Then it was so much fun that we just decided we wanted
그 때 우리가 기대했던
to keep doing it and see where it could go.
그것을 계속 어디로 갈 지 볼 수 있습니다.
This is the main area where people work,
이것은 사람들이 일 주요 영역이며,
where we have food team breakfast or lunch.
우리는 음식 팀의 아침과 점심을 가지고 있습니다.
At the beginning of the week we do where people get
주 초에 우리는 사람들이 어디에 가는지
to know each other and talk about what they're working
서로를 알고 그들이 일하고 있는지에 대해 이야기하기
on for the week.
일주일
Bean bag chairs, places people set up a workspace.
콩 가방 의자는 사람들이 작업 공간을 설정하는 곳.
It's pretty awesome to work here.
여기서 일하는 것은 정말 훌륭합니다.
You can sit here at the desk
당신은 여기에서 책상에 앉아 수 있습니다
and you'd be looking out over rice fields,
당신은 논을 바라보고,
and you can take a break and jump in the pool.
당신은 휴식을 취하고 수영장에서 점프 할 수 있습니다.
It's pretty ideal.
꽤 이상적입니다.
You can kind of get all your needs met here.
여기에서 당신의 요구를 모두 충족시킬 수 있습니다.
- I think the first time I really heard
- 내가 정말 들었을 때 처음
about digital nomads was probably
디지털 유목민 대해서는 아마
from “The 4-Hour Workweek”.
"4 시간제 워크 위크 '에서.
So many people found out about working and traveling.
많은 사람들이 일과 여행에 대해 알고있었습니다.
One of the reasons that I wanted to travel
내가 여행하고 싶었던 이유 중 하나
with a group like Hacker Paradise instead of just going
다만가는 것이 아니라, 박하 - 오버 파라다이스 같은 그룹과 함께
by myself was I mean first of all
내가 처음에 모든 것을 의미했다
because this is my first time doing the digital nomad thing,
이것이 디지털 유목민의 수를 처음으로하고 있기 때문에,
doing extended travel and working.
연장 된 여행과 협력하고 있습니다.
I wanted to find a community of people
나는 사람들의 커뮤니티를 찾고 싶었다
that are doing the same thing.
그것은 같은 일을하고있다.
One day I was sitting in my apartment in Montreal
어느 날 나는 몬트리올 내 아파트에 앉아 있었다
and it was minus 35, and I was like,
그것은 마이너스 35이었고, 나는
"I've had it, I've had enough."
"나는 그것을했다, 나는 충분히 가지고 있었다.
I went online and I looked up group trips for nomads,
나는 온라인으로 가서 유목민을위한 그룹 여행을 찾았습니다.
where nomads meetup a lot, and I found Hacker Paradise
어디에서 유목민이 모이는 것인지, 그리고 나는 Hacker Paradise
and I applied and 3 weeks later I got on the plane.
3 주 후에 나는 비행기를 탔습니다.
- Hubba is the first co-working space in Thailand
- Hubba 태국의 첫 번째 공동 작업 공간입니다
for a very long time.
매우 긴 시간입니다.
We were open since June 2012.
2012 년 6 월부터 오픈했습니다.
We’ve been for the past 3 years.
우리는 지난 3 년간 계속되고 있습니다.
Now, we’re in 6 locations.
지금 우리는 6 개소에 있습니다.
For Hubba, we’ve now have about 150 people coming here
Hubba 위해, 여기에서 150 여명이오고있다
every day and over each month, over 100 people visit us,
매월 매월 100 명 이상이 우리를 방문하고
take a tour of the space
공간을 둘러싼
and many do decide to come and work.
많은 와서 일을 결정한다.
We’ve got a great mix of both the expat
우리는 expat 모두 훌륭한 믹스를 가지고
and digital nomad community.
디지털 유목민 사회.
It comprises of approximately half of our membership
회원의 약 절반을 차지하고 있습니다
and the rest are Bangkokians or Thais in general
나머지는 일반적으로 방콕 인과 태국인입니다
from all across the country
전국 각지에서
that are working, living here in Bangkok.
일하고있는 방콕 여기에 살고있다.
- The idea of the Nomad Cruise is actually quite simple.
- 노매드 크루즈의 아이디어는 실제로 매우 간단합니다.
Instead of taking an airplane,
비행기를 타는 대신
we just meet on a cruise ship with over 100 digital nomads
100 명 이상의 디지털 유목민이있는 유람선에서 만날뿐입니다
and on the cruise ship we network, organize workshops,
유람선에서 네트워크를 만들고 워크숍을 개최하고,
conference and then when we enter the new continent,
우리가 새로운 대륙에 들어가면
we travel the continent together.
우리는 대륙을 함께 여행합니다.
We had all really very different skills.
우리는 정말 매우 다른 능력을 가지고있었습니다.
There not just programmers, not just copywriters,
카피라이터뿐만 아니라 프로그래머뿐만 아니라
but really everything.
하지만 정말 모든.
- If we wanted to dig into the cultural shift
- 우리가 문화의 전환을 발굴하고자한다면
and the mind shift,
마인드 변화,
you have to look at the development of technology.
당신은 기술의 발전을 봐야합니다.
Similarly you have now not just IM or Skype,
마찬가지로, IM 및 Skype뿐만 아니라
you have tools like Slack,
이완과 같은 도구가 있습니다.
you have all sorts of off-the-rack tools that you can use
당신이 사용할 수있는 모든 종류의 오프 랙 도구가 있습니다
to build very large companies
매우 큰 기업을 구축
without necessarily any headquarters,
반드시 본부가 없어도
without any of the traditional accouterments,
전통적인 부속품이 없어도
or architecture of a large company.
또는 대기업의 아키텍처입니다.
- In an old industrial context,
- 오래된 산업계에서는
people would tend to work closely with people
사람들은 사람들과 가깝게 일할 경향이 있습니다
who are very close to them
누가 그들에게 매우 가까이
and because this was the only way you could negotiate
이것이 당신이 협상 할 수있는 유일한 방법 이었기 때문에
what’s called mutual interdependencies.
상호 의존 관계라는 것.
So we need to able to talk to each other.
그래서 우리는 서로 이야기 할 수 있어야합니다.
If you only have a carrier pigeon
당신이 경력 비둘기가있는 경우
or a telegraph to communicate,
통신하기위한 전보,
if you have a lot of complicated work.
복잡한 작업이 많은 경우는
It will be a lot of pigeons going backwards and forwards.
전진과 후진의 비둘기가 많이있을 것입니다.
But of course with all
물론 모든
the modern communication technologies we have,
우리가 가지고있는 최신 통신 기술,
you could say a lot of these interdependencies
이러한 상호 의존 관계를 많이 말할 수 있습니다
can be replaced with the mediated communication.
중개 통신으로 대체 할 수 있습니다.
They can be replaced with mobile phone,
그들은 휴대 전화로 대체 할 수 있지만,
Facebook, Twitter, all of these things.
Facebook, Twitter,이 모든 것.
So if we look at this to build the teams,
팀을 만들기 위해 이것을 보면,
they have been coming from many, many, many years
그들은 몇 년 몇 년산
and the idea of having global development
글로벌 발상을 가진 아이디어
of products, of all social services,
제품 모든 사회 서비스,
global support for services and outsourcing,
서비스 및 아웃소싱의 글로벌 지원
offshoring, all of those things have happened
아웃소싱, 그 것의 모든 일이 있었
for 30, 40 years.
30, 40 년
- Most people who work today,
- 오늘 일하는 대부분의 사람들,
even if they're in an office are already working remotely.
비록 사무실에 있어도 이미 원격으로 작업하고 있습니다.
They're already using email remotely,
그들은 이미 이메일을 원격으로 사용하고 있습니다 만,
they're already using IM,
그들은 이미 IM을 사용하고 있습니다 만,
not everything is happening just in a face-to-face meeting.
얼굴을 삼가는 것만으로 모든 일이 일어나고있는 것은 아닙니다.
There's actually not that much out of a traditional office
실제로 전통적인 사무실 그렇게하지 않습니다
that you have to figure out,
당신이 파악해야 할 것은,
"Oh, how are we going to do that?"
"아, 어떻게해야하나요?"
- I had my first proper nine to five back
- 내가 먼저 적절한 9-5을했다
when I was I guess maybe 26 and after a few weeks
내가있을 때, 아마도 26 일 후와 몇 주 후
of having this Monday to Friday, nine to five.
이 월요일부터 금요일까지 9 시부 터 5 시까 지입니다.
I would be on the train, going to work, into the office
나는 기차를 타고 일을하고 사무실에 갈 것이다
and I would be thinking, “Wow, this is 30 minutes.
내가 생각하고있는 것 "와우, 이것은 30 분입니다.
"This evening 30 minutes.
"오늘 30 분.
"That’s 1 hour in a day.
"그것은 하루에 한 시간입니다.
"That’s 5 hours a week.
"그것은 일주일에 5 시간입니다.
"That’s 20 hours a month
"그것은 달에 20 시간입니다
"that I’m wasting sitting on public transport."
"나는 대중 교통에 앉아 낭비하고있다."
You live for the weekend,
당신은 주말에 살고 있습니다.
you can’t wait until you can finally go home
당신은 결국 집으로 돌아갈 수있을 때까지 기다릴 수 없습니다
and I was like, “What is this?”
나는 "이것은 무엇입니까?"와 같은 것이었다.
Getting rid of a commute gives you more time
통근을 제거하고 더 많은 시간을 얻을 수 있습니다.
to make dinner with my husband,
남편과 저녁 식사를 데리고
we have more time to hang out.
우리는 더 많은 시간이 있습니다.
We can have coffee in the morning
우리는 아침에 커피를 먹을 수 있습니다
and talk about our day instead of rushing off.
서둘러 아니라 오늘을 이야기합니다.
Often I will go out to meet friends
나는 종종 친구를 만나기 위해 나갈 것입니다
at rush hour for drinks.
러시아워에서 술을한다.
They'll get together at 5 or 6 p.m. after work,
그들은 5 ~ 6시에 모입니다. 퇴근 후,
and I'll find myself stuck in traffic,
나 자신이 교통에 붙어있는 것을 발견 것이다.
and I'm like, "What's happening?"
나는 "무슨 일이야?"
I totally forget that everyone else
나는 완전히 다른 사람이 잊지
in the world is commuting
세계에서 통근하고있다
and it's a totally normal experience
그것은 완전히 정상적인 경험입니다
that I just haven't had in so long that I totally forget.
난 그냥 내가 완전히 잊을 정도로 오래되지 않았습니다.
- It’s really, really becoming unaffordable and unobtainable
- 정말 정말 구할 수없는 정도 구할 수없는
for a lot of people in San Francisco.
샌프란시스코의 많은 사람들에게
What’s really happened in the last few years is
지난 몇 년 동안 정말 무슨 일이 있었나요?
that the epicenter of techs moved into the city.
기술자의 진원이 도시에 옮긴 것
San Francisco is a really small city
샌프란시스코는 정말 작은 마을입니다
and it has strict housing development guidelines.
어려운 주택 개발 지침을 가지고 있습니다.
The property development has just not happened
부동산 개발은 지금 일어나고 있지 않다
as the speed of people coming in and out.
사람의 출입 속도로.
What we’ve really seen is everything
우리가 정말 본적이 전부입니다
is gone up ridiculous amounts, salaries,
바보 금액, 월급,
commuting cost, living cost, rental, everything like that.
통근 비용, 생활비, 대여, 그런 것.
- We just look at the cost of living in San Francisco.
- 샌프란시스코에서의 생활비를 볼뿐입니다.
Now, all of those places, the average cost is $3,100.
그런데, 이러한 장소의 모든 평균 비용은 3,100 달러입니다.
$3,100 for a one bedroom apartment,
1 베드룸 아파트의 경우 3,100 달러,
that's not as nice as the one we have here for under 700.
그것은 우리가 700 세 미만인 위해 여기에 있 - っ하는 것만 큼 좋은 것은 없습니다.
Being from San Francisco,
샌프란시스코 출신으로,
my mom was a waitress in San Francisco,
나의 엄마는 샌프란시스코의 웨이트리스로
I think in the early 80s
나는 80 년대 초반에 생각
and she purchased a house on a waitress salary.
그녀는 웨이트리스 월급으로 집을 샀다.
Now, that house in a terrible neighborhood
지금 무서운 인근 집
in San Francisco is worth well over a million dollars.
샌프란시스코에서 100 만 달러 이상의 가치가 있습니다.
That doesn’t even make sense now
지금도 이해
because you can’t purchase a house.
집을 살 수 없기 때문입니다.
- The same in Holland.
- 네덜란드도 마찬가지.
Everybody comes to Amsterdam because of jobs.
일 때문에 모두가 암스테르담에 온다.
Over here, it’s overcrowded, overpriced,
여기에서는 그것은 혼잡하고, 비싸고,
if you want to live a cheaper life,
당신이 싼 생활을 위해서는
buy a cheaper house, you just go to the northern
싼 집을 구입, 당신은 북쪽으로 이동
or the south then you don’t have a job.
당신은 일이 없습니다.
So that’s the problem
그것이 문제입니다
and I think that’s the problem many countries are facing
많은 국가가 직면하고있는 문제라고 나는 생각한다
at the moment.
지금이 순간.
- Historically, every single person has been moving
- 역사적으로, 모든 사람이 움직이고 있습니다
towards better jobs, better career opportunities.
더 좋은 직장, 더 좋은 취업 기회 향해.
The entire history of economic migration
경제 전환의 역사
of the world has been about getting to where the jobs are.
일의 거점으로 다가오고 있습니다.
But at the same time there is now this complete new set
그러나 동시에이 완전한 새로운 세트가 지금이다
of people who can work anywhere
어디서나 일할 수있는 사람들의
which has not been possible before is
이전에는 불가능했던
that people have this liberty to move around
사람들이 자유를 가지고 다니는
and they can have a much more choice
그들은 훨씬 선택권을 가질 수 있습니다
about what other jobs they do locally,
그들이 현지에서 무엇을하고 있는지,
what other jobs they take with them
그들이 다른 어떤 일을하거나
and changing their location is the biggest lever they have
그들의 위치를 변경하는 것은 그들이 가지고있는 최대의 레버입니다
when changing their quality of life.
그들의 삶의 질을 바꿀 때.
- If you work online, you don’t need to be in the same area
- 온라인으로 일을하고있는 장소 - 경우, 동일 지역에있을 필요는 없습니다
like Rotterdam or Amsterdam, you can work wherever you like.
로테르담과 암스테르담처럼 - 원하는 곳에서 일을 할 수 있습니다.
You just need your laptop and that’s it.
당신은 노트북이 필요한뿐입니다.
You don’t have to be in this overcrowded, overpriced places.
이 붐비는 비싼 장소에있을 필요는 없습니다.
- Not everything has to happen in San Francisco.
- 샌프란시스코에서 모두가 생기는 것은 아닙니다.
Not everyone has to be here.
모두가 여기에있을 필요는 없습니다.
For people that want to live elsewhere and still access some
다른 곳에서 살고 싶은 사람
of the best tech companies in the world,
세계 최고의 기술 기업 중
working remotely is a really great option.
원격 조작은 정말 좋은 선택입니다.
- When I first wanted to become a digital nomad,
- 내가 먼저 디지털 유목민이되고 싶었던 때,
I researched all the options and ideas.
나는 모든 옵션과 아이디어를 연구했습니다.
I had found GitHub
나는 GitHub를 발견
which apparently is a developers dream job.
분명히 개발자의 꿈의 직업입니다.
Right now, GitHub is over 300 employees, around 300-350,
현재 GitHub는 300 명 이상 - 직원 약 300~350 명의 직원,
and over half are remote, and half are at headquarters.
절반 이상은 떨어져 있고 절반은 본부에있다.
If you live in San Francisco, you can also work from home,
샌프란시스코에 살고있는 경우 - 집에서 일을 할 수 있지만,
you can work at a coffee shop,
당신은 커피 숍에서 일할 수 있지만,
you can work anywhere you'd like.
당신이 좋아하는 곳에서 일할 수 있습니다.
In Morocco, I will be at this co-living,
모로코, 나는이 공동 생활 속에서
coworking space called SunDesk.
SunDesk라는 공동 작업 공간.
It's owned by a German girl
그것은 독일의 여자가 소유하고 있습니다
and it's a whole house.
그것은 집안이다.
Basically, we just have great internet,
기본적으로, 우리는 좋은 인터넷을 가지고 있습니다,
we work with other entrepreneurs, other companies
우리는 다른 기업, 다른 기업
and we just go sun and surf at the beach.
우리는 일출을 해변에서 서핑을합니다.
So I'll be safe.
그래서 안전합니다.
I'm not really alone.
정말 혼자가 아닙니다.
- Yeah, but do you know anybody over there?
- 그렇지만 누가 알아?
- [Amy] No.
- [Amy] No.
- You're just meeting people for the first time?
- 당신은 처음 사람을 만날 뿐입니 까?
- Yeah.
- 응.
My parents, they really support me.
부모님들이 정말 저를 지원하고 있습니다.
They love that I travel a lot.
그들은 내가 많이 여행하는 것을 좋아합니다.
They're okay with my adventurous spirit.
그들은 내 모험심 괜찮다.
They just wish I would pick very careful places.
그들은 그냥 아주 조심 장소를 선택하는 것을 희망한다.
- Well, 5 years ago I kind of thought
- 글쎄, 5 년 전에 나는 생각했다
I wanted her to be traditional,
나는 그녀를 전통적으로 원하는
but after 5 years now I kind of think
그러나 5 년 후에는 지금 내가 생각하고있는
it's a little different.
그것은 조금 다릅니다.
My whole thing is whatever makes her happy.
나의 모든 것은 무엇이든 그녀를 행복하게한다.
As long as she's happy, I'm happy.
그녀가 행복 할 한, 나는 행복합니다.
- I've been a digital nomad since 2009
- 나는 2009 년부터 디지털 유목민이었습니다
so about six years actually.
실제로는 약 6 년입니다.
I've been travelling for the last two and half years
난 지난 2 년 반 동안 여행하고 있습니다
with my girlfriend.
내 여자 친구와 함께.
There have definitely been a few really hard moments
물론 정말로 어려운 순간이있었습니다
especially in the beginning.
특히 초.
I mean for her, she had this huge life change
나는 그녀를 위해, 그녀는이 거대한 삶의 변화를 가지고
where she quit her job, was trying to start a business,
그녀는 일을 그만두고 사업을 시작하려하고있었습니다 만,
left her home country for the first time.
그녀의 모국을 처음 남겼다.
So you have all these major life changes going on
그래서 당신은 이러한 모든 중요한 삶의 변화가 일어나고있다
so that was incredibly stressful on her.
그것은 그녀에게 엄청나게 스트레스였습니다.
For me, I'd always traveled by myself.
나를 위해, 난 항상 자신을 여행했습니다.
Suddenly I'm traveling with my girlfriend
갑자기 나는 여자 친구와 함께 여행하고 있습니다
and it's completely different
그것은 완전히 다른
like you're having to make compromises all the time.
당신은 항상 타협을해야한다는 것입니다.
- If you're like,
- 당신이 좋아한다면,
"Uh, I quit my job to travel with you
"아, 나는 당신과 함께 여행하는 일을 그만 두었다
"and now my life is a mess."
"이제 내 인생은 혼란하고 있습니다."
Then it's the first thing that kills a relationship.
그리고 그것은 관계를 죽일 처음이다.
So if we have any hard moments in those.
그래서, 만약 우리가 그 안에 괴로운 순간이 있다면.
Oh, yeah.
그래.
I love cleaning and I love organized spaces.
나는 청소를 아주 좋아하고, 조직화 된 공간을 사랑 해요
Mark doesn't care.
마크 상관 없습니다.
He used to be like that 20 minutes before we leave a place,
그는 우리가 장소를 떠나기 전에 20 분 같은 것이었지만,
he would like, "Ah, I'm done",
그는 "아, 나는 끝났다"고 생각합니다.
and then he opens the suitcases like an atomic bomb.
그는 원폭 같은 가방을 엽니 다.
My suitcase is like he said, it's like a Tetris.
내 가방은 그가 말했듯이, 테트리스와 같은 것입니다.
I know exactly where everything is,
나는 모두가 어디에 있는지 정확히 알고,
and when I don't know, I start freaking out.
내가 모르는 때, 나는 미쳐 시작됩니다.
- What's wrong?
- 무엇이 문제인가?
- I have no idea where is my card.
- 내 카드는 어디에 있는지 모릅니다.
- Your bank card or your ID?
- 당신의 직불 카드 또는 당신의 신분증?
- No my bank card.
- 우리 은행 카드는 없습니다.
My ID is with you.
내 신분증은 당신과 함께합니다.
I'm a little desperate.
나는 약간 좌절입니다.
- This happens all the time.
- 이것은 항상 발생합니다.
- No, you're not taking me seriously?
- 아니, 당신은 심각하게 저를 데려가 않겠습니까?
- We found it.
- 우리는 그것을 찾아 냈다.
- Welcome to my world.
- 나의 세계에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
Like I feel like I'm going to have a stroke.
나는 스트로크를 갖도록 느낄 수 있습니다.
- It's like the boy who cried wolf,
- 그것은 늑대를 외쳤다 소년 같은 것입니다.
like she loses so much stuff all the time that like,
그녀는 항상 원하는대로 많은 것들을 잃고처럼
I don't even get worried.
나는 걱정하지 않는다.
I get worried when two hours go by,
2 시간이 지나면 나는 걱정한다.
because like 99% of the time she finds it
그녀가 찾아낸 시간의 99 %처럼
in the most obvious place.
가장 눈에 띄는 장소에서
- Five minutes, yeah.
- 5 분 그래.
- We actually realized at the time that it was like
- 우리는 실제로 그것을 좋아 때 알았다
if we survive this we're going to be okay?
우리가 이제 살아남 으면 우리는 괜찮을까요?
We did survive, it got better.
우리는 살아남은, 그것은 좋아졌다.
We started adjusting to each other.
우리는 서로 조정을 시작했다.
I think it's going to be interesting going forward
앞으로는 재미 있다고 생각
because, people, they want a long term relationships.
사람들은 그들이 장기적인 관계를하고 싶기 때문입니다.
They're getting more interested in marriage, kids.
그들은 결혼에 더 관심을 가지고 아이들.
I think this is going to raise a lot
나는이 많이 오른다 고 생각
of challenges and questions.
도전과 질문
I don't think anybody knows what's it going to look like
나는 그것이 무엇처럼 보이는지 아무도 모르는 것 같아요
but I definitely think this is going
확실히 이런 일이 있다고 생각
to become a major topic.
주요 항목된다
- We have two daughters.
- 우리는 2 명의 딸이있다.
Hannah, the bigger one, she was now in over 30 countries.
한나는 현재 30여 개국에 퍼져 있습니다.
The little one started a bit later,
작은 것은 조금 후에 시작
so I guess she has 10 or 12 countries less on her list.
그래서 그녀는 그녀의 목록에 10 가지 12 개국이 적다고 생각한다.
- For us, it was clear we want to have kids together,
- 우리를 위해, 아이들을 하나씩 - 함게하고 싶은 것은 분명했습니다.
but it was also clear we want to travel together.
함께 여행하고 싶은 것도 분명했습니다.
We were not sure from the beginning
우리는 처음부터 확신을 가질 수 없습니다
on how it will be to travel with kids.
아이들과 함께 여행하는 방법.
We decided that our first trip will be by car,
우리는 첫 번째 여행이 차에서 열리는하기로 결정했습니다.
that we can always come back if something happens.
무언가가 일어나면 언제나 건강하게 돌아올 수 있습니다.
We visited, I think, 11 countries at this time
우리는이 시점에서 11 개국을 방문했다고 생각합니다
and was very beautiful time of our life.
우리 삶의 매우 아름다운 때였습니다.
We decided that we have to make more kids and travel more!
우리는 더 이상 아이를 만들어도 - 계속 여행 할 필요가 있다고 결정했습니다!
They are used to different people,
그들은 다른 사람들에게 익숙하지만,
they are used to different languages.
그들은 다른 언어에 익숙해 져 있습니다.
They can speak three languages already now.
그들은 이미 3 개의 언어를 말할 수 있습니다.
They speak Polish with me, German with Tom,
그들은 저와 폴란드, 톰과 독일인,
and they learned English
그들은 영어를 배웠습니다
because we speak English with each other.
서로 영어를 때문입니다.
I also know that our kids really understand
나는 아이들이 정말 이해하고있는 것도 알고 있습니다
this definition of different.
다른이 정의.
For them, it's not only one language in the world
그들을 위해, 그것은 세계에서 하나의 언어 만이 아니다
or one way of people celebrating Christmas,
또는 크리스마스를 축하 사람들의 한 가지 방법은
because from the beginning on,
처음부터
they knew it can be very different.
그들은 매우 다를 수 있음을 알고 있었다.
- Kids can be really annoying when they said like,
- 어린이들이 좋아한다고 말 - 우와 정말 짜증나 될 수 있습니다.
"I want this!"
"이것은 싶어요!"
or "I don't want this!"
또는 "나는 이것을 싶지 않아!
and then they stand there and they will not walk.
그들은 거기 서서 걷는 것은 없습니다.
But this can happen anywhere.
그러나 이것은 어디서든 일어날 수있다.
That has nothing to do with trips but with personalities.
그것은 여행과는 관계없이 개성을 가지고 있습니다.
It doesn't depend too much on the circumstances
상황에 그다지 의존하지 않는
from my perspective.
내 관점에서.
I first communicated in other language when I was,
내가 먼저 다른 언어로 전한 것은,
I don't know, probably 17 or 18.
나도 몰라, 아마 17 또는 18.
It's incredible to see
보는 것은 믿을 수없는
how different beginning our kids have.
우리 아이가 어떻게 다른 시작됩니다.
- This idea of becoming digital nomads,
- 디지털 유목민된다는이 생각은
it didn’t really exist when we started thinking about this,
우리가 이것에 대해 생각하기 시작하면 실제로는 존재하지 않았습니다.
because people didn’t work remotely.
사람들은 원격으로 작동하지 않았다 때문입니다.
- It used to be that you had to either retire
- 이전에 퇴직 할 필요가 있었다
or put your life on hold in order to pick up stakes
말뚝을 데리러 당신의 생명을 지켜주십시오
and not be in the same place all the time.
항상 같은 위치에있는 것은 아닙니다.
- For us the biggest obstacle was my work.
- 우리의 가장 큰 장애물은 나의 일이었습니다.
My work in a law firm with clients
고객과의 법률 사무소에서 나의 일
in North Carolina was pretty rooted
노스 캐롤라이나에서 꽤 뿌리 있었다
in the idea of being present with those people.
그 사람들과 함께 있다는 생각에
We had to figure out a way to get that done
우리는 그것을 달성하는 방법을 이해해야합니다 없습니다
and to make clients feel like they were being taken care of
그들을 돌봐했다 같은 느낌을
even if I wasn’t going to be physically present.
내가 물리적으로 존재하는 생각은 없었다해도.
We moved toward having everyone on the team work remotely,
우리는 팀 전원에게 원격 - 에서 작업하는 것을 지시했습니다.
and we brought in a lot of new technology
우리는 많은 새로운 기술을 가져 왔습니다
into the business in order to facilitate remote work.
원격 작업을 원활히 진행하기 위해 사업에 도입한다.
We have spent years now putting all
우리는 몇 년에 걸쳐 모두
of those pieces in place so that I can sit here
나는 여기에 앉아있을 수 있도록 그 부분의 위치에
in Berlin or in a co-working space in Hong Kong
베를린에서 또는 홍콩 공동 작업 공간
and run the law firm just as I would have sitting
내가 앉아있는 것처럼 법률 사무소를 운영하는
in Raleigh, North Carolina.
노스 캐롤라이나 롤리에있다.
- We’ve been working on this for years,
- 우리는 몇 년 전부터 이에 대해 노력하고 있습니다 만,
and then we spent years getting rid of our house
그리고 우리는 몇 년 동안 우리의 가정을 제거했습니다
and getting rid of our possessions,
우리의 소유물을 제거,
and during this time we were preparing our children
그동안 우리는 아이들을 준비했습니다
to be adults.
어른이되는
I mean this didn’t happen overnight.
이것은 하루 아침에 일어나지 않았다는 것입니다.
- Being homeless is working out pretty well for us.
- 노숙자가 우리를 위해 잘 작동합니다.
- Yeah, exactly.
- 그래
When we started this process we talked a lot
이 과정을 시작했을 때, 우리는 많은 것을 이야기했습니다
about minimalism and materialism
미니멀리즘과 물질에 대해
and getting rid of our things independently of traveling.
여행과는 독립적으로 우리의 것을 제거한다.
- Going through this cleaning out
- 이것을 정화
of things has really caused us to reflect on materialism
물건 정말 우리에게 물질주의를 반영한
and to think about why we did all of the things that we did.
왜 우리가 한 일을 모두 짓을했는지 생각해보십시오.
I look at what I own which just literally fits
내 물건을보고 있습니다.
in in a carry-on, and I have nothing else in the world,
기내에서 전 세계에서 아무것도 없어,
I mean that's it.
나는 그것을 의미한다.
It just disturbs me that I spent so much energy
그것은 내가 너무 많은 에너지를 소비하는 것을 막을뿐입니다
and time thinking about wanting and searching for things
물건을 찾고 찾고있는 시간
and now I don’t have any of them and I don’t miss them.
지금은 그들 중 아무도 없어 - 하고 나는 그들을 놓칠 수는 없습니다.
So our experience is when we have a routine
그래서 우리의 경험은 루틴이있을 때입니다
and we’re living the same life,
우리는 같은 삶을 살고 있습니다.
those days do feel like they fly by.
그 날은 비행기처럼 느낀다.
When you get up in a new place each day
당신이 매일 새로운 장소에 일어날 때
and you have a new experience for breakfast
당신은 아침에 새로운 경험을하고 있습니다
and where you’re working and what you’re doing
당신이 일하고있는 곳은 뭘하는 거지
and somewhere interesting for lunch
점심 흥미로운 장소
and something different happens in the afternoon,
오후에는 뭔가 다른 일이 일어납니다.
and you go for a walk
당신은 산책
in a new neighborhood you’ve never been to that evening,
당신이 그날 밤에 가본 적이없는 새로운 지역에서는
and then you have ice cream at the place that you discover.
당신이 발견 한 장소에 아이스크림이 있습니다.
Boy, your days feel like weeks if not months,
소년, 당신의 날은 몇 개월이 아니라 주 같은 느낌,
and it really changes your perception of time.
정말 당신의 지각을 바꾸고 있습니다.
And as you get older,
당신은 나이가 먹을수록,
if there’s anything that you would want it's more time.
만약 당신이 원하는 것이 있다면, 그것은 더 시간입니다.
- My name is Joel Gascoigne,
- 내 이름은 Joel Gascoigne,
I'm the co-founder and CEO of Buffer.
나는 Buffer의 공동 설립자 겸 CEO입니다.
We all work, spread all across the world,
우리는 모든 일 전세계에 퍼져,
so right now we came together,
그래서 우리는 함께 와서
to be together for one and half weeks in Iceland.
아이슬란드에서 1 주일 반 동안 함께있는 것.
You kind of have that full spectrum of digital nomad
당신은 디지털 유목민의 전체 스펙트럼을 가지고 있습니다
where maybe travel for several months
어딘가 몇 달 동안 여행 할지도 모른다
and some people are just fixed in one location.
어떤 사람들은 단지 한 장소에 고정되어 있습니다.
Other people are traveling every couple of weeks.
다른 사람들은 2 ~ 3 주 간격으로 여행하고 있습니다.
I often don’t even know where somebody is,
나는 종종 사람이 어디에 있는지 몰라
so what we found is video calls are essential,
영상 통화가 필수적임을 알게되었으므로,
because you can see the facial emotions and everything.
당신은 얼굴의 감정과 모든 것을 볼 수 있기 때문입니다.
It's also why we have regular retreats every six months,
6 개월마다 정기적으로 퇴거하는 것도 무엇입니까?
we all come together in one place in the world
우리 모두 함께 세계 한 곳에 모여 있습니다
and spend a week and half together.
1 주일 반을 함께 보낸다.
You can always hear their voice when you read the emails
당신은 이메일을 읽을 때 - 항상 당신의 목소리를들을 수 있습니다
or the text based chat after the retreat.
또는 탈퇴 후 텍스트 기반 채팅.
That's why we found it has to be a combination,
그것은 우리가 그것을 결합 - 여야 않는 것을 발견 한 이유입니다.
we've got to come together regularly and there's benefits
우리는 정기적으로 함께 와야하지 않으며 이점이있다
like it's really great to work remotely
원격으로 작업하는 것은 정말 좋은
and in a distributed way as well.
분산 된 방식으로도 사용할 수 있습니다.
- Every time I go visit someone's fancy startup office,
- 내가 누군가의 화려한 시작 사무실을 방문 할 때마다,
I'm like, "Oh, yeah, this is really fun."
나는 "아, 이건 정말 즐겁다」라고 생각하고 있습니다.
It would be fun to visit for a while.
잠시 방문하는 것은 즐거운 것입니다.
I don't think I would want to stay.
내가 머물고 싶지 않다.
There's no better office for me than at home
집보다 나를 위해 좋은 사무실은 없습니다
or wherever I want to be.
사방에 있고 싶다고 생각합니다.
I think once you've had that freedom that remote work brings
나는 먼 일이 가져올 자유를 한번에
and had that different experience,
그 다른 경험을하고,
a whole different way of working,
전혀 다르게 작동 방법,
that feeling of productivity,
생산성 감,
I think that going back to traditional work might be hard.
나는 전통적인 일하러 것은 어려울지도 모른다고 생각합니다.
It might not feel as fun or as happy for me
그것은 나를 위해 재미 있거나 행복하게 느낄지도 모릅니다
as remote work does at Buffer.
원격 작업은 버퍼에서 수행되기 때문입니다.
- If you think about how much work you actually get done
- 당신이 실제로 얼마나 일을했는지를 생각한다면
at your full-time job, most people are not ashamed
당신의 풀 타임 직장에서 대부분의 사람들은 부끄러워하지
to tell you that I get 2 hours of work done a day,
나는 하루에 2 시간 일을하고 있는지를 전하기 위해
3 hours of work done a day.
1 일 3 시간 근무.
There is this joke about meetings for meetings
회의를위한 회의에 대한이 농담이 있습니다
and things like that.
그리고 그런 것.
Why force them to sit there, why force them to be at work.
왜 그들이 거기에 앉아 강제로 - 왜 그들은 일이되도록 강제한다.
You’re on Facebook or you’re on Reddit or Hacker News,
당신은 Facebook에 있는지, Reddit이나 Hacker News 있는지,
and you’re just wasting time because you’re not in the zone.
당신은 영역에 없기 때문에 시간을 낭비하고있을뿐입니다.
You’re not feeling what you need to be working on.
당신은 당신이 일하고있는 필요로하는 것을 생각하지 않습니다.
It’s the opposite as a digital nomad.
그것은 디지털 유목민과는 반대입니다.
You structure your life
당신의 삶을 구조화하는
around these little pockets of productivity,
이러한 작은 주머니의 주위에는
and they’re very productive.
그들은 아주 생산적입니다.
- Some managers think I have to be in the office
- 일부 매니저는 나가 사무실에 있어야한다고 생각한다
and I have to be able to physically see the people
나는 육체적으로 사람을 볼 수 있어야합니다
that I’m managing otherwise it doesn’t work.
나는 그렇지 않으면 작동하지 않습니다 관리하고있다.
How do I know if they work?
그들은 작동하는지 어떻게 알 수 있습니까?
You hire good people and you trust them.
당신은 좋은 사람을 고용, 당신은 그들을 신뢰합니다.
That’s how it works.
그것이 어떻게 작동합니까?
You verify their work product.
당신은 자신의 작품의 제품을 확인합니다.
Just physically being able to see whether somebody comes
물리적으로 사람이 오는지를 볼 수 있습니다
in exactly at nine or whether they stay past four.
다만 9시, 4시를 지나고 있는지.
It’s a very crude rudimentary even pre-civilization way
문명 이전의 방법으로도 매우 원시적 인 것입니다
of managing people like, “I can physically see you.
나는 육체적으로 볼 수 있습니다.
"I have line of sight.
"나는 시선을 가지고 있습니다.
"Thus I know that you’re working.”
"그래서 당신이 일하고있는 것을 알고있다.
Today is Monday, and we're a remote company,
오늘은 월요일, 우리는 떨어진 회사입니다,
and there's nobody at the office.
사무실에는 아무도 없습니다.
We have about 10, 12 people in Chicago,
시카고에는 약 10 명,
and some days there'll be a bunch of people,
어떤 날에는 많은 사람들이있을 것입니다.
maybe seven or eight people.
아마 7 명 8 명.
Twice a year, we fly everyone in and the office is packed,
1 년에 2 번, 우리 모두를 뛰어 올라 타고 사무실은 막혀 있습니다.
because we'll have about 50 people here.
여기에 약 50 명의 사람들이 있기 때문에.
This is pinning in everyone we had
이것은 우리가 가지고 있던 사람
at the company at the last meetup.
마지막 회의에서 회사에서
You see, there's a bunch of people spread out
당신이 보면, 많은 사람들이 퍼지고있다
all over Chicago, a couple people in Canada as well.
시카고 전역, 캐나다의 커플들.
Then the second biggest spot that we have is in the UK.
다음, 우리가 가지고있는 2 번째로 큰 장소는 영국입니다.
Me down here in the south of Spain.
나는 스페인의 남쪽 여기에있다.
One person in Australia.
호주의 한 사람
One person in Hong Kong.
홍콩의 한 명.
That's our map of the world.
그것은 세계의지도입니다.
When we started working together,
우리가 함께 일을 시작했을 때,
I was in Copenhagen, Denmark,
나는 코펜하겐, 덴마크,
seven time zones away from Jason here in Chicago
시카고 Jason에서 7 개의 시간대
and the rest of the team.
팀의 나머지 멤버
So the whole foundation story
그래서 전체의 기초 이야기
of Basecamp is one of remote work.
Basecamp의 원격 작업의 하나입니다.
Even though we actually have 10 or 12 people in Chicago,
시카고는 실제로 10 명 또는 12 명의 사람이 있습니다 만,
the bulk of them still work from home.
그들의 대부분은 여전히 집에서 일하고 있습니다.
They probably go to the office occasionally
그들은 아마 사무실에 갈 수 있습니다
because the office is an option.
사무실은 옵션이기 때문입니다.
It’s just a nice perk to have for the people who are here.
여기에있는 사람들을 위해 가지고있는 멋진 혜택입니다.
When we gather people up a few times a year,
1 년에 몇 차례 사람을 모으면,
it’s a great place to meet and hangout.
만날 수있는 완벽한 장소입니다.
But it’s entirely optional.
하지만 완전히 옵션입니다.
It’s expensive to buy a big office.
큰 사무실을 구입하는 비용입니다.
It’s expensive to relocate people.
사람을 이전하는 것은 비싸다.
It’s hard to relocate people.
사람을 이전하는 것은 어렵습니다.
To hire people all over the place,
그 위치의 사람을 채용,
it was just so much easier to let them be there.
그들이 거기에있는 것처럼하는 것이 훨씬 쉬웠다.
I think remote work works for all kinds of people.
나는 원격 워크는 모든 종류의 사람들을 위해 일할 것이다.
I think most people who have a job to do
일을하고있는 대부분의 사람들은
in front of the computer
컴퓨터 앞에서
or otherwise producing some sort of intellectual output.
또는 다른 방법으로 지적 출력을 생성 할 수 있습니다.
Yes, if you need to manage a machine,
네, 시스템을 관리 할 필요가있는 경우
and you need to stand there,
당신은 거기에 서해야합니다.
and you need to move things around,
당신은 물건을 움직일 필요가 있고,
of course you have to be near that machine,
물론, 당신은 그 기계 근처에 있어야합니다.
but less and less jobs are like that.
직업은 그렇게하지 않습니다.
More and more jobs these days are about sitting
최근 작품은 점점 증가하고 있습니다
in front of computer, communicating, collaborating,
컴퓨터 앞에서, 커뮤니케이션, 협업,
producing something in front of a computer.
컴퓨터 앞에서 뭔가를 만들어 내고 있습니다.
All the savings you can have on offices and so forth,
사무실에서의 절약 등
that's been one of the big drivers for other big companies
그것은 다른 대기업의 큰 드라이버 중 하나입니다
like IBM that's down-sized their offices
그들의 사무실을 다운 크기의 IBM처럼
because they let people work from home, and they realized,
그들은 사람들이 집에서 일하는 것을 허용하고 그들은
"We don't need as many desks.
"우리는 많은 책상을 필요로하지 않습니다.
"Oh, we can save a whole lot on real estate."
"아, 우리는 부동산 싶고 말이야 - 응의 수를 저장할 수 있습니다. "
- The rise of more and more jobs
- 더 많은 작업의 대두
that are remote work capable.
그것은 원격 작업이 가능합니다.
More jobs that get convergent information work.
수렴 한 정보를 얻을 일이 늘어납니다.
The more kinds of things you can do over
당신이 할 수있는 더 많은 종류의 것
an internet connection from anywhere.
어디서나 인터넷 접속이 가능합니다.
Obviously software development
분명히 소프트웨어 개발
but a little less obviously writing, law, graphic design
그러나 명확하게 작성하는 법, 그래픽 디자인
and then less obviously still overtime
그다지 분명 초과 근무하지 않은
as we get in robotic surgery.
우리는 로봇 수술을 받는다.
You can do medicine over an internet connection.
당신은 인터넷 연결을 통해 약을 할 수 있습니다.
Construction, you can operate drones
건설, 당신은 드론을 조작 할 수 있습니다
over an internet connection and things of that nature.
인터넷 연결과 성격을 통해.
You can be able to do more
당신은 더 많은 일을 할 수 있습니다
and more jobs over an internet connection.
인터넷 연결을 통해 더 많은 일.
As we start having software industry people
우리는 소프트웨어 산업의 사람들을 가지게되면
become more capable of doing remote work.
원격 작업을 할 수 있습니다.
- It’s interesting to see the trends about remote working.
- 원격 작업에 대한 동향을 보는 것은 흥미 롭다.
Some companies are really welcoming remote with open arms
일부 기업들은 오픈 팔을 원격지에 오신 것을 환영합니다
if you think about Dell is welcoming remote working
델이 원격 작업을 환영하고 있다고 생각한다면
and then it’s trickling down all the way to more companies.
그리고 더 많은 기업에 이르기까지 계속 흐르고 있습니다.
What we really get to see is the work flexibility
우리가 정말 눈에하는 것은 업무의 유연성이다
in the U.S. and across the world is really going up.
미국과 세계에서 정말 상승하고 있습니다.
More and more people are working
점점 더 많은 사람들이 있어요
for themselves or with more flexibility.
그 자체를 위해, 또는보다 유연하게.
- Automattic has a headquarters in San Francisco.
Automattic는 샌프란시스코에 본사를두고 있습니다.
We need some place to get mail and do meetings
우편물을 받아 회의를하는 장소가 필요합니다
but the vast majority,
그러나 대다수는
there’s only about 20 people there
거기에는 20 명 밖에 없습니다
so 95% of the company is outside San Francisco.
회사의 95 %가 샌프란시스코 밖에 있습니다.
Now close to 400 people all over the world
지금 전 세계적으로 400 여명
in over 47 countries.
47여 개국에 퍼져 있습니다.
We have always believed that great work,
우리는 항상 좋은 일,
collaboration, could be done online.
협업은 온라인으로 할 수 있습니다.
My name is Matt Mullenweg.
내 이름은 Matt Mullenweg입니다.
I'm the co-founding developer of WordPress.
나는 WordPress의 공동 설립자입니다.
- Why would I ever try to uproot people
- 왜 나는 사람들을 근절하려고 했습니까?
and move them to San Francisco or build just an office
샌프란시스코로 이동하고 있었다 - 한 사무소를두고 할 수 있습니다
and only hire people here?
여기에서 사람을 고용 뿐입니 까?
It's obvious that there's so many amazing people
많은 놀라운 사람들이 분명하다
all over the world, and I want to work with them.
전세계의 사람들과 함께 일을하고 싶다고 생각하고 있습니다.
The internet is pretty good,
인터넷은 괜찮은 편이고,
why not just hire people wherever they are?
그들이 어디에 있든 사람들을 고용하는 이유는 무엇입니까?
- For me, working remotely is essential.
- 나를 위해, 원격 조작이 필수적입니다.
I'm really bad at going to an office.
정말 사무실에가는 것이 나쁜 것입니다.
I can't do it.
나는 그것을 할 수 없습니다.
After around two weeks of going
약 2 주 후
to the same place I get stir crazy and don't do anything.
같은 장소에 내가 미쳐 흔들리고 아무것도하지 않는다.
I'm also really bad living in one place
나는 또한 정말 나쁜 곳에 살고있는
because after around a month of being somewhere
어딘가에있는 것이 약 1 개월 후
I get really bored and start having a week of burnout
정말 지루한 일주일 번 아웃을 시작
where I just sit and watch TV or something.
그냥 앉아서 TV 나 무언가를 본다.
I am much happier as a person and more productive
나는 사람으로 더 행복하고 더 생산적입니다
in the long-term if I had the ability to,
내가 능력을 가지고 있으면, 장기적으로는
every few hours be like,
몇 시간에 1 번,
"I'm going to go take a break now
"지금은 휴식거야
"for 30 minutes and see something new."
"30 분 동안 새로운 것을 보라."
I just find that, in general,
나는 일반적으로
helps my particular style of working a lot more.
내 특정 스타일의 작업에 많은 도움이됩니다.
- One interesting stat, since joining Zapier more than half
- Zapier에 절반 이상 참여 이후 하나의 흥미로운 통계
of the people have moved and moved
사람들의 이동과 이동
to a completely different city.
전혀 다른 도시에
Even from people who are from families
가족의 사람들도
and so that’s kind of I think the lifestyle affordances
내가 라이프 스타일 어포던스라고 생각하는 것입니다
that remote gives you makes it a lot easier
그 리모콘은 당신에게 더 쉽게합니다
even if you have a family and a little bit settled.
비록 당신이 가족과 조금 화해했다고해도.
It makes it a lot easier to decide,
그것은 결정하는 것이 훨씬 쉽습니다 만,
we are going to move a little bit closer to our family,
우리는 가족에 조금씩 접근 생각입니다 만,
a family member who gets sick
아프면 가족
or something like that because we can.
그렇게 할 수 있기 때문입니다.
We don’t have to worry about the hassles of resigning
사임의 번거 로움을 걱정할 필요가 없습니다
from this job and finding a new job elsewhere.
이 작품에서 다른 위치로 새로운 일자리를 찾을 수 있습니다.
They can just pick up and move somewhere else if need be.
그들은 필요에 따라 주워 다른 위치로 이동 할 수 있습니다.
- There's companies that are finding new ways
- 새로운 방법을 모색하고있는 기업이있다
to work that allow people to set their own hours,
사람들이 자신의 시간을 설정할 수 있도록 일,
have more flexibility, live wherever they want in the world,
그들은 세계 어디에서나 살 수 있습니다.
and they're going to attract the best people in the world
그들은 세계 최고의 사람들을 유치 예정입니다
because the best people
최고의 사람들
in the world are largely going to think,
세계에서 대부분 생각하려고하고 있지만,
"Why do I have to commute to Mountain View every day
"매일 마운틴 뷰에 통근해야하는 이유는 무엇입니까
"and sit in a bunch of meetings and things like that?
"그리고 그러한 회의와 물건을 잔뜩 앉아있다?
"Maybe I want to live in Mountain View part of the year,
"나는 올해의 마운틴 뷰의 일부에 살고 싶은지도 모르지만,
"but maybe during the summer I want to go to Italy
"그러나 여름에는 이탈리아에 가고 싶다
"or to Thailand or Australia, or wherever it is."
"태국, 호주, 또는 그 어디에 있어도."
It doesn't matter, it's just giving them the flexibility
그것은 중요하지 않습니다, 그것은 그들에게 유연성을 제공하고있을뿐입니다
to be in control of their own life.
자신의 인생을 지배한다.
In the future they will either be distributed
미래 그들은 배포되는지
or they'll be overtaken by companies that are
또는 기업이 추월하게됩니다
because the smartest people in the world are going
세계에서 가장 똑똑한 사람들이가는 때문입니다
to want to work this way.
이와 같이 일하고 싶다
- Something that it took me three or four years
- 나에게 3 년 또는 4 년 걸렸다
to start to realize is
실현을 시작하는
that this is a very extreme lifestyle.
이것은 매우 극단적 인 라이프 스타일이라고 생각합니다.
This is a lifestyle that is constantly bombarding you
이것은 당신에게 항상 충격을주고있는 라이프 스타일
with new experiences and new perspectives.
새로운 경험과 새로운 관점에서
And this can be very powerful,
그리고 이것은 매우 강력한이며,
but what I've discovered is that it can be very powerful
하지만 내가 발견 한 것은 그것이 - 매우 강력한 수 있다는 것입니다
both in a positive and negative way.
모두 긍정과 부정의 방법으로
The idea was basically by working online,
이 아이디어는 기본적으로 온라인으로 작업하여
by being an entrepreneur working remotely
원격지에서 일하는 기업가 인에
you can build all this freedom and independence
당신은이 모든 자유와 독립을 구축 할 수 있습니다
for yourself that you couldn’t do before.
이전에는 할 수 없었던 자신을 위해.
The nature of that idea allows for this kind
그 아이디어의 본질은 이러한 것을 가능하게하는
of pyramid scheme to open up underneath them.
피라미드의 아래에 그들을 여는 데.
- “Are you sick of your ordinary boring life?
- "당신은 보통의 지루한 생활에 싫증이 있습니까?
"Are you tired of doing stuff you don't like
"당신이 좋아하지 않는 것을 할 일에 싫증 있습니까?
"and being stuck in your stupid cubicle everyday?
"바보 같은 방에 매일 막혀 있습니까?
- “Oh my god. I need to start a website
- "뭐라고 것이다. 나는 웹 사이트를 시작할 필요가있다
"or start a company that will let me live anywhere I want.
내가 어디서나 원하는 곳에 살지 - 시켜주는 회사를 시작하십시오.
"What do I talk about?
"내가 무엇에 대해 이야기합니까?
"I have no idea.
"아무것도 생각 나지 않습니다.
"I’ll just write about going and living the dream
"난 그냥가는 꿈의 생활에 대해 쓰기
"and living on a beach and following your own passions
"그리고 해변에 살고 자신의 열정에 따라
"and all this stuff.”
"와 이러한 모든 것.
Then they go out and they write that.
그리고 그들은 나와 그들은 그것을 씁니다.
They stumble across it and they pay this person money
그들은 발생, 그들은이 사람에게 돈을 지불
and all these people are like, “Where do I start?”
이 사람들은 모두 "나는 어디에서 - 시작합니까? "라고하는 것입니다.
“I don't know.
"모르겠어요.
"I’ll start a website about how to take more control
"더 컨트롤하는 방법에 대한 웹 사이트를 시작하는
"of your life and how to live in a beach.”
"당신의 삶과 어떻게 바닷가에 사는 하나"
This pyramid scheme opens up
이 피라미드 열립니다
and it fills out these deeper and deeper niches.
이러한 깊고 깊은 틈새를 메운다.
- There’s a lot of people
- 많은 사람이
that have an over optimistic view of,
지나치게 낙관적 인 전망을하고있다,
“Hey, let’s come to Southeast Asia,
"이봐, 동남아시아에 갑시다.
"live cheap, drink party and do all sorts of naughty stuff
"싸게 살 파티를 마시 - 모든 종류의 나쁜 일을
"and have an amazing time."
즐거운 시간을 가질 수 있습니다 "
- I feel like sometimes people misinterpret that.
- 때때로 사람들이 그것을 오해하는 것 같은 생각이 든다.
They’re always writing these stupid Medium articles
그들은 항상이 바보 같은 매체 기사를 쓰고있다
and articles that they want posted about,
그들은 게시 싶은 기사,
“Quit your job and live in Thailand for $50 a day.”
"일을 종료하고 1 일 50 달러로 태국에 살고있다"
That doesn’t work for everyone.
그것은 누구에게도 잘못된다.
- A lot of people are making money off
- 많은 사람들이 돈을 벌
of selling you the digital nomad lifestyle dream.
당신에게 디지털 유목민 생활의 꿈을 파는 것.
They want you to buy their $39 eBook to sell you the dream
그들은 당신에게 당신의 꿈을 팔기 위해 $ 39 eBook을 구입 원한다
because they’re living in Bali and they need money too.
그들은 발리에 살고 있고, 돈도 필요하기 때문입니다.
There’s a lot of hype about it that it doesn’t live up to.
그것은 그때까지 살아 있지 않은 것에 대해 과대 광고가 있습니다.
It’s really more like do you prefer living in an apartment,
당신이 아파트에 사는 것을 선호 정말 더 비슷하지만,
in a city or do you prefer living in a house in the country?
당신은 나라의 집에 살고있는 분을 좋아합니까?
It’s not that one is better than the other,
그것은 다른 것보다 낫다있는 것은 아닙니다,
it’s just that these are different lifestyles.
이들은 서로 다른 라이프 스타일이라는 것뿐입니다.
- You’re not going to automatically become rich just
- 당신은 자동으로 부자가 될 수는 없습니다
because you live in a cheaper country.
당신이 싼 나라에 살고 있기 때문입니다.
It really depends on what you’re working on,
정말 당신이 종사하고있는 무슨에 의존합니다.
how would you monetize,
어떻게 수익을 창출 하시겠습니까?
how well do you understand the market,
당신은 시장을 얼마나 잘 이해하고 있습니까?
how well are you solving the problems.
얼마나 잘 문제를 해결하고 있습니까?
- One of the tricky part is when you live on the road,
- 어려운 부분 중 하나는 당신이 도로에 살 때입니다.
every second months like I’m doing right now is
내가 지금하고있는 같은 2 개월마다
the one sentence I’m saying very often
나는 매우 자주 말을 한 문장
when I get to meet someone is,
내가 사람을 만날 수 있다면,
“I will be leaving in two weeks.”
"나는 2 주 후에 떠날 것이다"
Loneliness is the real thing.
외로움은 사실입니다.
For many reasons when you are in your home country,
당신이 모국에있을 때 많은 이유로
and it’s a Friday night, you can just pick up the phone,
그것은 금요일 밤, 당신은 나비 - 어느 전화를 픽업 할 수 있습니다,
call a friend, see what’s happening
친구에게 전화해서 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는지 볼
or just walk to your local bar.
또는 당신의 지역의 술집에 걸어.
When we’re in some place completely different,
우리가 완전히 다른 위치에있을 때,
being in a small village or in a huge city doesn’t matter.
작은 마을이나 큰 도시에있는 것은 문제가 없습니다.
It’s really much harder for you to be connected.
당신이 연결하는 것은 정말 훨씬 어렵습니다.
- Sometimes the weekend was suddenly calm
- 때로는 주말이 갑자기 평온했다
and I’ve not planned any activity,
나는 활동을 계획하고 있지 않다,
I have not reached out and tried to meet people
나는 손을 뻗어 있지 않고, 사람들을 만나려고 한
and it’s just really hard.
정말 어렵습니다.
I didn’t have anything to do.
나는 아무것도 할 필요가 없습니다.
Sometimes that would just be really lonely feeling
가끔은 그냥 정말 외로운 기분이 될 것입니다
and I felt really quite down with more than I’ve ever felt.
지금까지 이상으로 많은 것을 느꼈습니다.
- It’s really hard.
- 정말 어렵다.
Long distance relationships really suck
장거리 관계는 정말 짜증
and it’s hard to find interesting people.
재미있는 사람을 찾기가 어렵습니다.
That’s tough.
그것은 힘듭니다.
I haven’t fixed that one.
나는 그것을 수정하지 않습니다.
- I hear a lot about from single nomads
- 나는 하나의 유목민에서 많이 듣는
about being lonesome.
약 외롭다.
Being married is a huge advantage.
결혼하는 것은 큰 장점입니다.
Being a couple, being nomadic,
연인임을 유목민이다,
because you just don’t have that issue.
당신은 그 문제를 가지고 있지 않기 때문입니다.
You aren’t going to be lonesome.
당신이 고독하게 될 것은 없습니다.
You may have to go out and build other relationships outside
나가서 다른 관계를 구축해야 할지도 모릅니다
of the marriage but you’ve always got somebody
당신은 항상 누군가를 가지고
that you can go back and talk to.
당신은 다시 말할 수 있습니다.
To me that makes this really easy.
나를 위해 정말 간단합니다.
Now at the same time, we laugh about this,
동시에, 우리는 이에 대해 웃어요,
because all the young nomads,
모든 젊은 유목민들
they’re all on Tinder dating everybody that they can date.
그들은 모두 그들이 데이트 할 - 그리고있는 모든 사람과 만나고있다.
- Swipe, swipe.
- 슬쩍 슬쩍.
- That's also one of the disadvantages
- 그것도 단점 중 하나입니다
of being a married nomad.
결혼 한 유목민임을
- We have each other to bounce things off of,
- 우리는 서로 물건을 跳ね返さ하고
I always have a calming influence when I’m freaking out
난 항상 온화한 영향력을 가지고 있습니다.
about how hot it is or the taxi that didn’t show up on time
그것이 얼마나 더운 또는 시간에 표시되지 않은 택시에 대해
or the train that’s stuck in the middle of nowhere
또는 중간에 붙어 있던 열차
and I don't know where we are, whatever the issue is,
문제가 무엇이든간에, 우리가 어디에 있는지 모르겠지만,
because there are going to be issues, I have backup.
문제가 생길 수 있기 때문에 나는 백업을 가지고 있습니다.
- If things don’t work out I can always swipe.
- 일이 잘못되면, 나는 - 항상 출근 할 수 있습니다.
- You can swipe. - Swipe right.
- 당신은 슬쩍 수 있습니다. - 오른쪽으로 스 와이프합니다.
- One of the big topics of conversations
- 대화의 큰 화제 중 하나
between me and nomad friends,
저와 유목민의 친구 사이에,
and also friends at home is relationships, or like,
또한 가정의 친구 관계 나,
"How is your love life?
"당신의 사랑 생활은 어떻습니까?
"How is dating?"
"데이트는 어때요?"
I do have to say it is harder than normal.
난 보통보다 어렵다고한다.
I've talked to many, many friends, girls and guys,
나는 많은 많은 친구, 소녀,
about dating, and a lot of them are like,
만남에 대해서, 그리고 그 대부분은
"Amy, you have to stay somewhere for a decent amount of time
"에이미, 당신은 괜찮은 시간에 어딘가에 있어야한다
"to begin dating and meet someone to stay
"데이트를 시작하고 누군가를 충족 머물
"with them long term."
"그들과 장기간"
I think that's the dilemma with nomads today.
나는 그것이 오늘의 유목민의 딜레마라고 생각한다.
When you're sick and traveling around the world,
당신이 병으로 세상을 여행하고있을 때,
you still want people around.
당신은 여전히 주위의 사람들이 갖고 싶습니다.
When you're having a bad day,
나쁜 하루를 보내고있을 때,
you still want friends and family and people
당신은 여전히 친구와 가족, 그리고 사람들이 원하는
to be thinking of you.
당신을 생각하고있다.
- I definitely think this lifestyle
- 확실히이 라이프 스타일을 생각
complicates dating in many ways.
여러 가지 방법으로 데이트를 복잡하게한다.
Most digital nomads they’re still pretty young
대부분의 디지털 유목민은 아직 젊은
and we’re all aging together and what I’m noticing
우리 모두 함께 나이 들어 내가 눈치가
as the years go on,
올해 진행됨에 따라,
this is becoming more and more of an issue.
이것은 점점 문제가되고 있습니다.
A lot more people are talking about it
더 많은 사람들이 그것에 대해 얘기하고있다
and are getting frustrated about it.
그것에 대해 불만을 품고 있습니다.
- Where loneliness now becomes more of an issue
- 외로움이 이제 더 문제가되고있는 곳
is with the other two problems, isolation and depression.
다른 두 가지 문제, 고립과 우울증이 있습니다.
If loneliness starts to get too intense,
고독이 강해지기 시작하면,
people can start to feel isolated
사람들은 고립 느낄 수있다
especially if they’re in a culture
특히 그들이 문화 속에있는다면
where they don’t speak the language
그들은 언어를 말하지 않는 장소
and they don’t know anyone that sense
그 감각을 아무도 모른다
of isolation will eventually turn into depression.
고립 결국 우울증으로 바뀐다.
Where you’re born or where you live doesn’t always have
당신이 태어난 곳과 사는 곳이 반드시있는 것은 없습니다
that much of an impact on your mental health.
그것은 당신의 정신 건강에 큰 영향을 미칩니다.
What does have a positive impact on your mental health
당신의 정신 건강에 긍정적 인 영향을 미칠 것
though is having a community,
커뮤니티를 가지고 있어도,
having again that support network of people
사람들의지지 네트워크를 다시 가질
that you can access.
액세스 할 수 있습니다.
It’s really about forming that network.
정말 그 네트워크를 형성하는 것입니다.
That can happen anywhere.
그것은 어디서나 일어날 수있다.
That doesn’t have to be where you grew up and where you went
그것은 당신이 자란 곳과 목 - 이 갔 일 필요는 없습니다
to school or where you happen to be living in that moment.
당신이 그 순간에 살아있는 장소 나 학교에 갈 수 있습니다.
- If you’re a guy living this lifestyle
- 당신이 라이프 스타일로 사는 사람이라면
and you start to get lonely,
당신은 고독 해지기 시작합니다.
it’s very easy to fall into this trap of just like,
그냥 같이이 함정에 빠지는 것은 매우 쉽습니다,
some of these countries,
이들 국가의 일부는
like prostitutes are very inexpensive
매춘부 같은 것은 매우 저렴합니다
so you see a lot of guys falling into that trap.
그래서 당신은 그 함정에 빠지지 많은 사람들을 본다.
- “Meet hot girls and party like crazy"
- "섹시한 여자와 미친듯한 파티를 만난다"
- Guys who have never actually experience that intimacy
- 그 친밀감을 실제로 경험 한 적이없는 사람
or like a healthy dating relationship,
또는 건강한 만남 관계처럼,
they don’t realize that.
그들은 그것을 인식하지 않습니다.
They just assume, dating is just about sex
그들은 단순한 일이라고 생각한다.
and these girls want to have sex with me so why not.
이 여자는 나와 섹스하고 싶어서 그렇게해야합니까?
- Sex tourism is always prevalent in Southeast Asia,
- 섹스 관광은 동남아시아에서는 항상 유행하고 있습니다 만,
low income communities across the world.
세계의 저소득층 커뮤니티.
There’s a lot of women that are forced into it.
그것을 강제하는 여성이 많이 있습니다.
There’s a lot of issues around the mafia.
마피아 주변에는 많은 문제가 있습니다.
There’s loads of women that are digital nomads,
디지털 유목민 인 여성이 많아
that are part of this community,
이 커뮤니티의 일원이며,
and also the LGBT community,
또한 LGBT 커뮤니티,
and we have to be mindful that some of the things
우리는 몇 가지가 신경 쓰이는해야합니다
that a lot of the digital nomads take for granted
많은 디지털 유목민 당연한 일이다
and think that it's an all-male community
남녀 공동 참가 사회라고 생각한다
or male-dominated makes it uninclusive
또는 남성이 지배하고있다
and repulsive for some people.
어떤 사람들은 반발한다.
- It’s a danger of a lifestyle
- 그것은 생활의 위험
that definitely is tabooed to talk about.
확실히 금기 것으로 알려져있다.
Not many people talk about it openly but yeah,
많은 사람들이 그것에 대해 공개적으로 이야기하는 것은 아니지만,
it’s an issue and I think more people should talk about it.
그것은 문제이며, 더 많은 사람 - 들이 그것에 대해 이야기해야한다고 생각합니다.
- A sexpat is a guy who’s here just to,
- 성별 패드는 단지 여기에있는 남자,
maybe he’s an older gentleman.
아마 그는 연상의 남성입니다.
He wants to hit on young Thai girls.
그는 젊은 태국 여자 치고 싶어.
Enjoy the underground sex industry here in Thailand.
여기 태국 지하의 섹스 산업을 즐길 수 있습니다.
These are the people we don’t want.
이들은 우리가 원하지 않는 사람들입니다.
How do we differentiate a digital nomad from that guy?
어떻게 우리는 그 남자와 디지털 유목민을 구별합니까?
These are the sort of things that we have to think about
이들은 우리가 생각해야 할 것입니다
and actually start coming up with solutions for in order
실제로 차례로 해결책을 생각하고 있습니다
to actually obtain some sort of Visa program
실제로 어떤 종류의 비자 프로그램을 얻을
for the digital nomads.
디지털 유목민을 위해.
These are the tough questions that needed to be asked
이 질문 할 필요가있는 어려운 질문입니다
and come up with solutions from in order
부터 순서대로 해결책 마련
for it to be implemented.
그것을 실현하기 위해
- Visas have been such a challenge because you look online
- 당신이 온라인으로 보이기 때문에, 비자는 도전하고 있습니다
and the Visa information is never up to date.
비자 정보는 최신이 아닙니다.
- And they change it every 6 months.
- 그리고 그들은 6 개월마다 그것을 변경합니다.
There needs to be a universal visa.
보편적 인 비자가 필요합니다.
Just let me pay some money a lot of money, I don’t care.
그냥 돈을 많이 지불 해 주면, 난 상관하지 않습니다.
Give me a universal visa
나는 보편적 인 비자를 전달
and make it easier and put it online.
그것을 더 쉽게 온라인으로 할 수 있습니다.
- They’re here on a tourist visa
- 그들은 관광 비자로 여기에
and they’re always doing all these tourist visa runs,
그들은 항상 이러한 모든 관광 비자를하고 있으며,
go to the border, come back, or some of them
국경에 가서 돌아올 또는 그 일부
they go a different route, let’s say to get education visa.
그들은 다른 길을가는 교육 비자를 취득하려고합시다.
Some of them, they go to a Thai language school
그들 가운데는 태국의 어학 학교
and they’ll become a student for Thai language
그들은 타이어의 학생이 될 것입니다
and then they go, “We’re a student visa,”
그들은 "우리는 학생 비자입니다"
but then they never go to classes.
그러나 그들은 클래스에가는 것은 아닙니다.
I mean look if you want to stay in Thailand,
당신이 태국에 남고 싶어한다면,
you want to be here for a longer period of time,
당신은 오랫동안 여기에 있고 싶어,
maybe you should consider how can you pay taxes?
어쩌면 당신은 어떻게 세금을 지불 할 수 있을까요?
If you pay taxes, that is a direct indicator
세금을 지불하고 그것은 직접적인 지표입니다
that you want to be a contributing member society.
당신이 공헌 한 회원 사회가되고 싶다
“Please stay in my country but you don’t pay taxes.
"내 나라에 머무는 동안, 당신은 세금을 내지 않는다.
"You don’t give us anything.”
"당신은 우리에게 아무것도주지 않았다"
That doesn’t sound like a good business pitch.
그것은 좋은 비즈니스 피치처럼 들리지 않습니다.
There are complicated legal questions
복잡한 법적 문제가 있습니다
when you’re dealing with tax issues,
세금 문제를 다루고있는 경우
with immigration issues.
이민 문제가
- The one thing that I can say with absolute certainty is
- 내가 절대 확실하게 말할 수있는 것은,
that you do not want to rely on the advice of people
당신은 사람들의 조언에 의지 싶지 않아
who are not well versed and trained in
누구에게도 익숙하지 않으며 훈련되지 않은
and licensed in dealing with these issues.
이러한 문제를 해결하기 위해 라이센스되어 있습니다.
I see it a lot on blogs and in various forums
나는 블로그와 다양한 포럼에서 그것을 많이 볼
where nomads will ask for answers from other nomads
유목민은 다른 유목민의 답변을 요구
and that just make no sense at all.
그것은 전혀 의미가 없습니다.
Someone’s experience as an individual is interesting
개인적으로 사람의 경험은 재미
and illuminating but you really want to get your answers
비추어 있지만, 당신은 정말 당신의 대답을 얻고 자
from somebody that is well versed in this system.
이 시스템을 잘 알고있는 사람으로부터.
Interesting story.
재미있는 이야기.
Our son is in Thailand and was dealing
우리 아들은 태국에 있고, 거래했습니다
with the hopping in, hopping out visa run issue
비자 발급 문제를 뛰어
and I said to him, every month I would say,
나는 그에게 말했다 매월 나는 말할 것이다,
“Talk to an immigration lawyer.”
"이민 변호사와 상담하십시오."
He would say, “No, I’ve talked to some guys,”
그는 "아니, 난 어떤 남자와 얘기"라고합니다
and I was, “Talk to an immigration lawyer."
나는 "이민 변호사와 상담하십시오"라고했습니다.
Finally after a year of doing visa runs, coming and going,
마지막으로, 비자 교환 출입,
he finally talked to an immigration lawyer
그는 마침내 이민 변호사와 얘기를했다
and what do you know, the immigration lawyer had answers
당신은 무엇을 알고 있습니까? 이민 변호사 답변이있었습니다
to his questions and solutions to his problems.
그의 문제에 대한 질문과 해결책에.
- There’s very low compliance and tax laws
- 준수 및 세법이 매우 낮은
to begin with Indonesians and then also foreigners.
인도네시아 인과 외국인으로부터 시작된다.
A lot of foreigners are here and they’re not clear
많은 외국인이 여기에 있고, 그들은 분명하지 않은
about what the tax rules are.
세금 규칙이 무엇인지.
If they try to find out what they are, it’s very confusing.
그들이 무엇을 찾으려고하면 그것은 매우 혼란합니다.
Most people just choose to put their head in the sand
대부분의 사람들은 단지 자신의 머리를 모래 속에 두는 것을 선택
and ignore the regulatory environment.
규제 환경을 무시합니다.
I think it’s really interesting for governments
정부에게 정말 재미 있다고 생각
around the world as all of these type of movement,
이러한 모든 유형의 움직임으로 세계에서
this type of migration is happening.
이런 종류의 전환이 이루어지고 있습니다.
You go on a holiday for two weeks to the United States
당신은 미국에 2 주 휴가를갑니다
and you’re managing your business in China, are you working?
당신은 중국에서 당신의 사업을 관 - 리하고 있습니다, 당신은 일하고 있습니까?
Do you need a work permit for that?
당신을위한 노동 허가가 필요합니까?
I think probably not.
아마 없다고 생각한다.
It’s not clear.
그것은 명확하지 않습니다.
- The government will get you eventually
- 정부가 궁극적으로 당신을 얻을 것이다
if the numbers are high enough for the government to care.
정부가 처리하기에 충분한 숫자가 있으면.
You want to figure out what the laws are.
당신은 법률이 무엇인지 파악하고 싶다.
You want to figure out who you owe, you want to comply.
당신은 당신이 빌린 사람을 알고 - 싶다, 당신이 보호하고 싶다.
You want to pay what you owe and stay in compliance
당신은 당신이 의무 - 를 지불하고 준수를 유지하려면
with all the applicable laws.
적용되는 모든 법률이 적용됩니다.
It is better to do what you’re supposed to do now
당신이 지금하려고하는 일을하는 것이 좋다
rather than worry about when they’re going
그들이 언제 가는지 걱정하는 것이 아니라
to catch up with you later.
나중에 따라와.
- It bugs me how unconscious a lot of people.
- 그것은 많은 사람들이 무의식 중 - 어떻게 무의식적으로 버그 하는가?
I’ve heard conversations between people where they brag
나는 그들이 자랑하고있는 사람들 사이의 대화를 들었다
about how they don’t have to pay for visas
그들이 비자를 지불 할 필요가없는 방법
and they brag about how they don’t have to pay taxes
그들은 그들이 세금을 지불 할 필요가없는 방법을 자랑하고 있습니다
and some of the places.
어떤 장소.
These people are living in a country for two, three years.
이 사람들은 2, 3 년간 국가에 살고 있습니다.
There’s starving kids all around
주위에 굶주려있는 아이들이있다
and they’re bragging about they don’t have to pay taxes
그들은 세금을 지불 할 필요가 없다고 자랑하고있다
and they hired a maid for 50 cents an hour or whatever.
그들은 1 시간에 50 센트 또는 어떻게 든 메이드를 고용했다.
It’s just like know where you’re living.
당신이 사는 곳을 아는 것과 같습니다.
Know what you’re participating in
당신이 참가하고있는 것을 알
because whatever country you choose to spend time in,
당신이 시간을 보내고 어느 나라를 선택해도
you are participating in that society, in those systems.
이러한 시스템에서, 당신은 그 사회에 참여하고 있습니다.
I do believe in the benefits of this lifestyle
나는이 라이프 스타일의 혜택을 믿습니다
and I do believe in a lot of the philosophical ideas
나는 많은 철학적 아이디어를 믿습니다
behind it but I feel like
그 뒤에, 나는 생각이 든다
there’s no ethical voice talking about it.
그것에 대해 이야기 윤리적 인 목소리는 없습니다.
- Yeah, I agree.
- 그래, 난 동의합니다.
There is a bit of a problem when we look
볼 때 약간의 문제가 있습니다
at how it’s mostly the digital nomad lifestyle
어떻게 그것이 주로 디지털 유목민의 생활 양식인가?
is a very western phenomenon or for the rich white kids
아주 서양적인 현상인지, 풍부한 백인 아이들에게
who can go off and travel the world
누가 나가서 세계를 여행 할 수 있는가?
and run an online business and take advantage
온라인 비즈니스를 실행하고 활용하는
of all the great facilities and the infrastructure
모든 훌륭한 시설과 인프라
and all these developing countries.
이러한 모든 개발 도상국.
I get that.
나는 그것을 얻는다.
That is a fertile ground for criticism.
그것은 비판의 비옥 한 근거입니다.
That’s something we need to look at.
그것은 우리가 볼 필요가있는 것입니다.
- I see all these articles that pushing people
- 나는이 모든 기사를보고 사람들을 눌러
to travel around the world.
세계 여행
I have a friend who lives in India and he is a nomad.
나는 인도에 사는 친구가 있고, 그는 유목민입니다.
He wants to be a nomad,
그는 유목민이되고 싶다,
but being a nomad for him is so much more difficult
그러나 그의 유목민 인 것은 훨씬 더 어렵다
than it is for me.
그것은 나를 위해입니다.
I am an American citizen,
나는 미국 시민이지만,
and I am very fortunate to have a very powerful passport,
나는 매우 운이 매우 강력한 여권을 가지고,
in the terms that it lets me visit most countries
내가 대부분의 국가를 방문 할 수 있다는 조건
with very flexible dates of when I can leave.
내가 떠날 수있을 때 매우 유연한 날짜.
I can stay at one place for 90 days.
나는 한 곳에서 90 일간 체류 할 수 있습니다.
With him, he was only given like a week,
그와 함께, 그는 일주일처럼 주셨습니다 만,
and he gets easily denied to stay longer.
그는 쉽게 거부 오래 머물 수 있습니다.
It's because the country that he is from,
그가 출신 인 나라는
the passport is not considered as powerful.
여권은 강력하다고 간주되지 않습니다.
That just, it really sucks.
그냥 정말 안됐다.
- This is kind of the cutting edge of what's happening now.
- 이것은 지금 일어나고있는 최첨단 같다.
It's a very new and exciting thing.
그것은 매우 새롭고 흥미로운 것입니다.
Generally, cutting edge things start in the richest parts
일반적으로 최첨단 것은 가장 풍부한 부분에서 시작됩니다
of the world because you have people who are educated
교육을 받고있는 사람들이 있기 때문에 세계
and wealthy enough to take these kinds of risks
이러한 종류의 위험을 감수 정도로 부유층
and try these new things.
이러한 새로운 것을 시도하십시오.
- These great programmers
- 이러한 위대한 프로그래머
from all over the world come to Thailand,
전세계에서 태국에 와서
how do you transfer your skills on to the locals?
당신의 능력을 어떻게 현지인들에게 전하고 있습니까?
How you get them excited about programming?
어떻게 프로그래밍에 흥분합니까?
How do you mentor people so that they learn from you?
당신은 어떻게 사람들을 가르치고, 그들이 당신에게서 배우나요?
These are the types of people we want to see come in here.
이들은 우리가 여기에 오는 것을보고 싶은 사람의 유형입니다.
- When I came here, I hosted a NodeSchool
- 내가 여기 왔을 때, 나는 NodeSchool
for local developers to learn Node.
로컬 개발자가 Node를 배우기 위하여.
Some people came and if they can learn how
몇몇 사람들이 와서 그들이 어떻게 배울 수 있는가?
to make their own technical stuff,
그들은 자신의 기술을 만들기 위해,
then I’m not needed anymore to be here.
나는 더 이상 여기있을 필요는 없습니다.
That’s really helpful.
정말 유용합니다.
It’s also like I’m trying to build a website
또한 나는 웹 사이트를 구축하려고하고있는 것 같습니다
for a taxi driver here because I feel like I want
택시 운전사를 위해 여기에 내가 원하는대로 느끼기 때문에
to help them out.
그들을 돕기 위해.
There’s different ways of ameliorating the problem
문제를 개선하는 다양한 방법이 있습니다
of just being a guy who comes in,
들어온 사람이라는 것뿐만 아니라
spends some money and leaves.
돈과 잎을 보낸다.
As long as we’re cognizant of that, I feel better.
우리가 그것을 인식하고있는 한, 나는 기분이 좋아집니다.
- Digital nomads can be professional,
- 디지털 유목민은 전문가도
they can be remote-working,
그들은 원격 조작 할 수 있으며,
they can be building million dollar products,
그들은 백만 달러의 제품을 쌓을 수,
they can be working on distributed teams
그들은 분산 된 팀에 임할 수 있습니다
on unicorn start-ups across the world,
전세계 유니콘의 신흥 기업은
they can be some of the most amazing people to talk to.
그들은 이야기하는 사람 중 가장 놀라운 사람 중 한명입니다.
- Let’s look at a world where Star Trek existed,
- 스타 트렉이 존재하는 세계를 살펴 보자.
the federation of planets and what not.
행성의 연합이란 무엇인가.
You didn’t have borders.
당신은 국경을 가지고 있지 않았습니다.
They didn’t have nationalities.
그들은 국적을 가지고 있지 않았습니다.
They were Earth.
그들은 지구이었다.
They just existed and they all lived in peace
그들은 단지 존재하고 그들은 모두 평화롭게 살았다
and they just went everywhere.
그들은 어디든지 갔다.
If the world is going to move in that direction,
세계가 그 방향으로 움직이는한다면,
what Gene Roddenberry imagined
Gene Roddenberry가 상상 한 것
way, way back in the ‘60s, the digital nomad lifestyle
60 년대 디지털 유목민 라이프 스타일
is one pathway that we can get there.
우리가 거기에 도착할 수있는 하나의 방법입니다.
It’s pretty awesome.
꽤 훌륭합니다.
- If you think about this
- 이에 대해 생각한다면
from the businessman point of view,
사업의 관점에서 보면,
I mean what are your options.
당신의 선택은 무엇입니까?
If you want to get more having more profit,
더 많은 이익을 얻기 위해서는,
you most probably need more customers.
당신은 아마 더 많은 고객을 필요로합니다.
(light music)
(경음악)
We have 1.3 million Estonians,
우리는 130 만 명의 에스토니아 인,
and what are our ways to increase our customer base?
고객 기반을 확대하기위한 우리의 방법은 무엇입니까?
We basically need more people.
기본적으로 더 많은 사람이 필요합니다.
If you don’t have those services
이러한 서비스를 가지고 있지 않은 경우
that you need in your country available,
사용 가능한 국가에서 필요한 것,
but those service are available location independently
이러한 서비스는 독립적으로 사용할 수 있습니다
from another country.
다른 나라에서.
That’s where the e-residency concept comes from.
그것은 e 레지던시의 개념이 어디에서 오는지입니다.
(light music)
(경음악)
- After 20 hours of this launch page,
-이 시작 페이지의 20 시간 후
we received over 4,000 early subscribers
우리는 4000 명 이상의 조기 가입자을 받았습니다
who want to become e-residents from 150 different countries.
150 개국에서 전자 주민되고 싶은 사람.
It totally spread, word of mouth, just tweets.
그것은 완전히 확산 구어 역, 그냥 짹짹.
It was amazing.
그것은 놀라운 것이었다.
All together this package, this company,
이 패키지이 회사,
bank account, service provider, digital signature means
은행 계좌, 서비스 제공 업체, 디지털 서명 방법
that you can run location independent business.
당신은 장소에 관계없이 비즈니스를 수행 할 수 있습니다.
The e-Estonia showroom gets three delegations per day
에스토니아의 쇼룸은 하루에 3 개의 임무를 얻습니다
for that reason, because Estonia has been successful
그 이유로, 에스토니아는 성공하고있다
in all e-Estonia solutions.
모든 에스 솔루션에서 사용할 수 있습니다.
We are helping to help other countries
우리는 다른 나라
to also implement those platforms
이러한 플랫폼을 구현하는
and get those services there.
그 서비스를 거기에 도착합니다.
Estonia also benefits.
에스토니아에 관심이 있습니다.
If everybody, every country would be so digital
모두 모든 나라가 디지털적인면
and then you could start communicating
다음 커뮤니케이션을 시작할 수 있습니다
with each other very easily.
서로 매우 편리합니다.
For example, send e-tax reports automatically
예를 들어, 전자 세금 보고서를 자동으로 전송
between every country
국가 간
and everybody would pay taxes automatically,
모두가 자동으로 세금을 낼 것이다,
everything would be great here.
여기에서는 모든 위대한 것입니다.
It would be everybody's benefit
모두의 이익이 될 것이다
that more countries would be more flexible,
더 많은 나라가 더 유연,
more innovative in that sense.
그런 의미에서 더 혁신적인입니다.
- How to get more foreign investment, how to get best talents.
- 더 많은 외국인 투자를 얻으려면 - 은 어떻게 최고의 인재를 얻을 수 있습니다.
Estonia, we have found our way to compete in this war
에스토니아, 우리는이 전쟁에서 경쟁하는 방법을 찾았습니다
and providing best services to the citizens
시민에게 최고의 서비스를 제공하는
and most convenient and affordable services.
가장 편리하고 저렴한 서비스입니다.
- E-residency program are emblematic concerns
- E 레지던스 프로그램은 상징적 인 관심사입니다
where governments are going to be going
정부가 어디로 가는지
in the next maybe not five years but 10, 20 years
다음 5 년이 아니라 10 년, 20 년
because what they’re trying to do is they’re trying
그들이하려고하는 것은 그들이 시도하고 있기 때문입니다
to compete for the kind of folks
사람들을 위해 경쟁하는
who are likely start businesses,
누가 사업을 시작 가능성이 높거나
bring wealth and jobs and so on to their society.
풍요 로움과 고용 등을 사회에 제공합니다.
This is actually putting governments into competition
이것은 실제로 정부를 경쟁에 맡기고있다
with each other in a new way.
서로 새로운 방법으로.
There is a really important paradigm shift
정말 중요한 패러다임의 변화가 있습니다
as you move from the government to a government.
당신이 정부에서 정부로 전환함에 따라
It seems to move from the company to a company.
그것은 회사에서 회사로 전환하는 것 같습니다.
Once you are mobile, a government is just a provider
일단 당신이 모바일되면 정부는 단순한 업체입니다
of natural resources rule sets.
자연 자원 규칙 세트
Cultural things that date to the fact
사실과 날짜를 기록한 문화적 일
that it used to be a geographical entity.
그것은 이전에는 지리적 인 존재였다.
More and more people will move.
점점 더 많은 사람들이 움직이는 것입니다.
They’ll pick the government that suits them best
그들은 그들에게 가장 적합한 정부를 선택할 것이다
at this particular time and place.
이 특정 시간과 장소에서.
It means they'll move later in life.
그들은 인생의 후반으로 이동하는 것을 의미합니다.
- We're still learning about the best way
- 우리는 여전히 최선의 방법을 배우고있다
to set up global work forces and things like that.
글로벌 인력과 같은 것을 설정한다.
I think if you get some big successes,
난 당신이 몇 가지 큰 성공을 거둔 후
people will start to, you know.
사람들은 시작 것입니다, 당신은 알고 있습니다.
Companies who may have thought that the only way
유일한 방법이라고 생각했을지도 모른다 기업
to run an organization was with a giant headquarters
조직을 운영하는 것은 거대한 본부를했다
in one location and might start
하나의 위치에 시작할 수 있습니다
to think there's different ways
다른 방법이 있다고 생각
to do things and experiment a little bit more.
일을하고 좀 더 실험하십시오.
- More and more companies they do realize they need to adapt
- 그들은 그들이 적응해야 - 있다는 것을 실감 점점 더 많은 기업
and they need to be more innovative
그들은 더 혁신적 일 필요가 있습니다
and make their employees happier
직원을 더 행복하게
by giving them more freedom.
그들에게 더 많은 자유를 제공함으로써.
- The fact is people want to work in more flexible ways,
- 사실, 사람들은 좀 더 유연한 방식으로 일하고 싶다고 생각하고 있습니다.
in different ways than they've been working
그들이 일하던 것과는 다른 방식으로
for the last 10, 20, 40, 100 years.
지난 10 년 20 년 40 년 100 년
Ever since the industrial revolution.
산업 혁명 이래.
This idea of working in these massive offices
이러한 대규모 사무실에서 일한다는이 생각
in a corporate environment is no longer appealing
기업 환경에서 더 이상 매력이 없습니다
to many, many people.
많은 많은 사람들에게.
I think digital nomads might be the extreme example,
나는 디지털 유목민이 극단지도 모른다고 생각하지만,
but they're an example of how the world is changing.
그러나 그들은 세계가 어떻게 변화하고 있는지의 예입니다.
- The world is going to get a lot more remote
- 세계는 더 멀리 될 것이다
for various reasons.
여러 가지 이유로.
We have good enough technology
충분한 기술이 있습니다
that people can stay in touch all the time.
사람들은 항상 접할 수 있습니다.
Society in general is just more excited about travel,
일반적으로 사회는 여행에 흥분하고 있습니다.
excited about seeing new places, visiting new places.
새 위치를 볼 수 새로운 장소를 방문하게 된 것을 기쁘게 있습니다.
- I think people might assume the place they grow up
- 나는 사람들이 그들이 성장하는 위치를 추측 할지도 모른다 생각
is where they should be.
그들은 어디해야합니까?
You might be a lot happier somewhere else.
당신은 다른 곳에서 더 행복 할지도 모릅니다.
If you go and explore and try other places,
당신이하고 탐구하고 다른 장소를 시도하고,
you might find somewhere
당신은 어디에서 찾을 수 있습니다
where it just feels like a much better fit
훨씬 더 잘 맞는 느낌 위치
for you as a person.
사람으로 당신을 위해.
Who's to say that the place
누가 그 자리를 말하고 있나
that you grew up is the place that you're meant to be?
당신이 자란 것은 당신이 의도 된 장소는?